Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Po was eating her Tubby Custard
Tubby custard! Tubby custard!
Uh-oh!
Oh dear! Po had Tubby Custard
all over her hand
Oh dear Tubby Custard hand urghh
Po didn't know what to do
Don't know what do
Po made a print with her hand
Po print hand
Again again
Another hand print
'nother hand print
Again again
Another hand print
Po liked making hand prints
hand prints!
Po made lots of prints
on the table
Again again
how decorative
And then Po decorated
the Tubby Toaster
Look decorate toaster
Again again
how decorative
So Po decorated the doors
Ohh
Decorate door
Decorate
Again again
how decorative
Ahh
Look
So Po decorated the steps
Decorate steps
Again again
Decorate
how decorative
Then Po heard somebody coming
Somebody coming
Eh-oh
Po showed Tinky Winky Dipsy and
Laa-Laa her hand print decorations
Look decorations
Ohh
Look
Look decorations
Ohh
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
thought Po's hand print
decorations were beautiful
Ohh beautiful
And then the Noo-noo tidies up
Oww Noo-noo!
Noo-noo
Owww Noo-noo
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland
it was noisy footsteps day
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky walked indoors
Walked indoors
Eh-oh
Dipsy walked along the path
Walk along the path
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa walked over the hills
And Po rode her scooter
Scooter
Po scooter
What a noisy footsteps day
Too noisy too noisy
And so the Teletubbies
tried to walk quietly
Tinky Winky tried
Tinky Winky walk quietly shh
Shh
Dipsy tried
Dipsy walk quietly shh
Laa-Laa tried
Laa-Laa walk quietly shh
Shh
Eh-oh
Po tried
Scooter quietly shh
Shhh
What a quiet footsteps day
Oh dear
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa Po
Uh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa
and Po were marching
Ohh marching
Tinky Winky marched with his bag
Tinky Winky march with bag
Ohh
March march march march
Yee!
Dipsy marched with his hat
Dipsy march hat
Ohhh
March march march
hooray Dipsy yes
Laa-Laa marched with her ball
Laa-Laa march the ball
Ohh
March march march
Yee!
Po marched with her scooter
Po march scooter
Ohh
Yee!
Teletubbies love to march
Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug
Tinky Winky
Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland
the Noo-noo was tidying up
when he heard somebody coming
Eh-oh
Look at Laa-Laa's knees
Uh-oh!
Laa-Laa's knees are all dirty
Laa-Laa knees all dirty Uh-oh!
Two dirty knees
Somebody's coming
Somebody coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Look at Dipsy's knees
Uh-oh!
Dipsy's knees are all dirty
All dirty uh-oh
One two three four dirty knees
Somebody's coming
Somebody coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Look at Tinky Winky's knees
Uh-oh!
They are all dirty
All dirty
Uh-oh!
One two three four
five six dirty knees
Six dirty knees
What are we going to
do with six dirty knees?
Oh er em
It's time for Tubby Sponges
Tubby Sponges! Tubby Sponges
May we have the Tubby Sponges
It's time for the Teletubbies
to wash their dirty knees
with their Tubby Sponges
Tubby sponges
Six dirty knees
Wash them clean
Wash wash wash
Tubby tubby tubby
Oh Tubby sponges Tubby sponges
hooray Tubby Sponges!
hooray Tubby Sponges
There Laa-Laa's knees
are all clean now
Laa-Laa knees all clean now
Ohh
Four dirty knees
Wash them clean
Wash wash wash
Tubby tubby tubby
Tubby sponges
There Dipsy's knees
are all clean now
Dipsy knees all clean
Ohh
But Tinky Winky
has still got dirty knees
Dirty knees
Tubby sponge
Wash wash wash
Tubby tubby tubby
There Tinky Winky's knees
are all clean now
Tinky Winky knee all clean
Ohh
No dirty knees
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Look at Po!
She's dirty all over
Po dirty all over
Tubby sponges!
Uh-oh!
Tubby sponges
One dirty Po
Wash her clean
Tubby sponges!
Wash wash wash
Tubby tubby tubby
Teletubbies love
their Tubby sponges
There now Po's all clean
Po all clean
Uh-oh!
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye