Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies had
their favourite things
Tinky Winky had the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy had the hat
Dipsy hat
Po had the scooter
Scooter
But wait a minute
where's Laa-Laa's ball
Oh
Uh-oh!
Oh no! Where the ball
Laa-Laa hasn't go the ball
Oh no
Biddly cheese
where the ball
So everybody
looked for the ball
Laa-Laa ball
Oh Eh-oh
Oh where the ball
Ball!
Oh where the ball?
Looking here and looking there
Tubbies looking everywhere
Laa-Laa's ball
Laa-Laa's ball!
Yess!
Oh the ball Oh the ball
hooray
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies had
their favourite things
Dipsy had the hat
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa had the ball
Laa-Laa ball
Po had the scooter
Scooter
But wait a minute
where's Tinky Winky's bag
Uh-oh!
Where Tinky Winky bag
Tinky Winky hasn't
got the bag
Oh no!
So everybody looked for
Tinky Winky's bag
Tinky Winky bag
Oh Tinky Winky bag?
We haven't got it
Tinky Winky bag
Oh dear oh dear
Oh dear
Looking here
Looking there
Tubbies looking everywhere
Oh look
Tinky Winky's bag
Tinky Winky bag look
Tinky Winky bag
Tinky Winky bag!
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies
had their favourite things
Tinky Winky had the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Laa-Laa had the ball
Laa-Laa ball
And Po had the scooter
Scooter
But wait a minute
where's Dipsy's hat?
Uh-oh!
Oh no all gone where hat
Dipsy hasn't got the hat
Oh no
hat where hat
So everybody looked for
Dipsy's hat
Dipsy hat
Oh l say there is no hat here
hat where hat hat where hat
hat where hat
Looking here and looking there
Tubbies looking everywhere
Dipsy hat
Look
Dipsy's hat
Dipsy hat
Yes Dipsy hat
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies had
their favourite things
Tinky Winky had the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy had the hat
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa had the ball
Laa-Laa ball
But wait a minute
Where's Po's scooter?
Scooter
Uh-oh!
Where scooter
Po hasn't got her scooter
Oh no
Po scooter
So everybody looked for Po scooter
Oh l say!
We don't even like scooters
Where scooter
Looking here and looking there
Tubbies looking everywhere
Look look
Po's scooter
Po scooter
hooray Po's scooter
Scooter
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies had
their favourite things
Tinky Winky had the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy had the hat
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa had the ball
Laa-Laa ball
And Po had the scooter
Scooter
All the Teletubbies had
their favourite things
Yeeeee
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Po was eating here Tubby Toast
when she heard a funny sound
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Po
Laa-Laa had come to
play with her ball indoors
play with ball indoors
Uh-oh!
Ball ball
hooray ball
Laa-Laa liked playing
with the ball indoors
Laa-Laa like play
with ball indoors nice
Ball
Uh-oh!
Quick Po
help Laa-Laa catch the ball
Ball! Ball!
Eh-oh
Quick Tinky Winky
help Laa-Laa and Po catch the ball
Dipsy was asleep all the time
Quick Dipsy help
Laa-Laa catch the ball
Quick Dipsy
Ball!
Oh no naughty Noo-noo
Naughty Noo-noo
Look at that
The Noo-noo helped Laa-Laa
catch the ball
Noo-noo catch the ball
Ahh Noo-noo Big hug
Big hug!
Teletubbies love the
Noo-noo very much
Teletubbies love
the Noo-noo very much
Uh-oh!
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky sang a special song
into his bag
Song in bag
There what a lovely song
Lovely song
Tinky Winky opened the bag
to see if the song was inside
Song inside
What a lovely song
to have in your bag
Lovely song in bag
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky wanted to
show Dipsy the song in his bag
Show Dipsy song bag
Ohh
Dipsy look
There
Ohh
Dipsy wanted to sing a special
song into Tinky Winky's bag
Dipsy special song
Tinky Winky bag
Yes here are
There what a lovely song
Lovely song
Tinky Winky opened the bag
to see if the song was inside
Song inside
What a lovely song to
have in your bag
Lovely song
Thank you Dipsy
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky hadn't gone very far
when he heard another song
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky wanted to
put Po's song in the bag
Po song bag
Oh Po song bag
here are
There what a lovely song
Lovely song
Tinky Winky opened his bag
to see if the song was inside
Song inside
What a lovely song to
have in your bag
Lovely song in bag
Lovely song
Thank you Po
Bye bye Po
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
Ohh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky wanted to
put Laa-Laa's song into his bag
Laa-Laa song in bag
Laa-Laa song in bag?
Ohh
Laa-Laa's song
Er um um
here are Tinky Winky
There what a lovely song
Lovely song
Tinky Winky opened his bag
to see if the song was inside
Song inside
See if song inside
What a lovely song
to have in your bag
Lovely song in bag
Lovely song
Thank you Laa-Laa
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky has four songs
in his bag
Four songs in bag
Laa-Laa's song
Po's song
Dipsy's song
And Tinky Winky's song
Tinky Winky song
Tinky Winky was very happy
to have so many songs in his bag
Songs in bag
Be careful Tinky Winky
Mind the songs!
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky opened the bag
Open bag uh-oh
The songs were all mixed up
All songs mixed up oh no
What a lovely mixed up song
to have in your bag
Lovely mixed up song in bag
Teletubbies love songs
Again again
Ohh
Teletubbies love each other
very much
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for a song
all about Dipsy's hat
Dipsy's hat Dipsy's hat
Fancy that
lt's Dipsy's hat
Eh-oh
hat
Dipsy Dipsy come along
We're all waiting for the song
hurry up and put it on
ha-at ha-at ha-at hat!
Dipsy's hat
Dipsy hat
Fancy that it's Dipsy's hat
Dipsy's walking with his hat on
Very proudly in to view
lf you had a hat like that on
You'd be walking proudly too
Dipsy's hat
Dipsy hat
Fancy that it's Dipsy's hat
Dipsy's walking with his hat on
Very proudly in to view
lf you had a hat like that on
You'd be walking proudly too
Fancy that Dipsy's hat
Dipsy hat
Dipsy's walking with his hat
Far over the hills on a windy day
What out Dipsy
hat's like that are liable
to blow away
hat! hat! hat!
Dipsy's hat Dipsy's hat
Fancy that
lt's Dipsy's hat
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies
were very busy
Very busy busy busy very busy
Very busy very busy busy
Tinky Winky had the bag
Bag
Dipsy had the hat
hat Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa had the ball
Laa-Laa ball ball
Laa-Laa ball
And Po had the scooter
Eh-oh
Where's Po's scooter?
Uh-oh!
Scooter
There's Po's scooter
Eh-oh
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky had the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy had the hat
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa had the ball
And Po had the scooter
Uh-oh!
Where's Po's scooter?
Where's Po's scooter
There's Po's scooter
Scooter
Po loves her scooter
Oh no! The scooter's coming
Po's scooter
Uh-oh!
Run away!
Po loves her scooter and
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo! (Laughs)
Boo he-he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye