Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Teletubbies
Say hello
hello
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Teletubbies
Big hug
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
E-oh
One Po
Po hurray Po hurray
Two Pos
Three Pos
Four Pos
Five Pos
E-oh
Four Pos
Three Pos
Two Pos
One Po
Whey whey whey bye bye
E-oh
oh ooh look What's that?
Ooh What's that?
Star
Ooh Star Star star star star
Star star star star star star
hee hee star
Star
E-oh Yeah ha ha Tinky Winky
Ooh Ooh Ooh E-oh
E-oh
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
E-oh
One day in Teletubby land
something appeared from far away
What's that?
lt was a bluebell
Oh Bluebell Bluebell
E-oh
E-oh La La
E-oh Po
Bluebell
Pardon
Bluebell Look
Ooh Ooh Look
Bluebell
Yes
Ooh ooh Oh Bluebell
Bluebell
Then another bluebell appeared
Ooh Ooh
Another bluebell
And another and another
Another and another
Bluebells bluebells
E-oh
E-oh Tinky Winky E-oh Dipsy
E-oh La La E-oh Po
Ooh What's that?
Bluebell
Ooh bluebell
Yes
Ooh Ooh
Another bluebell
Oh oh Another bluebell
Bluebells
Lots of bluebells
Bluebells everywhere
Bluebells Everywhere
Dipsy went for a walk
among the bluebells
Dipsy walk bluebells
La-La danced among the bluebells
La-La dance in bluebells
Tinky Winky smells the bluebells
Tinky Winky smells bluebells
Tinky Winky smell bluebells
Po sang a bluebell song
Po bluebell song
Bluebell bluebell bluebell
bluebell bluebell
Bluebell
And then the bluebells disappeared
all gone all gone all gone
Big hug
Big hug Ahh Big hug
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
E-oh
One day in Teletubby land
it was time for Tubby toast
Ooh Tubby toast tubby toast
Tubby toast tubby toast
O-oh
Oh no the Noo Noo tidied up
the Tubby toast
Noo Noo tidied up toast
Naughty Noo Noo
O-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Oh Tinky Winky
E-oh
One day in Teletubby Land
it was time for Tubby custard
Tubby custard Tubby custard
Tubby custard
O-oh
Ooh look
Look at that
A Tubby Custard bubble
Bubble
Tubby Custard bubble
Bubble bubble bubble bubble
Oh dear
the Tubby Custard bubble burst
E-oh
Look at that
All the Tubby Custard bubbles
have burst
The Noo Noo tidied up
Away go the bubbles
Bye bye bubbles
Bye bye bubbles Bye bye
Big hug
Teletubbies love each other very much
E-oh
One day in Teletubby Land
Dipsy was watching
Dipsy watching
Dipsy watched the windmill turning
Dipsy watch windmill
Dipsy watched the rabbits playing
Dipsy watch rabbits
Dipsy watched the trees in the wind
Dipsy watch trees
Then Dipsy heard somebody coming
Somebody coming
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch
lt was La-La
La-La
E-oh
La-La danced a lovely dance
Oh La-La dancing lovely dance
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch
Lovely dance Ahh
What a lovely dance
Lovely dance
Then Dipsy heard
somebody else coming
Somebody coming
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch
lt was Po
lt Po
E-oh
Po sang a special song
Special song
Po po po po Po po po po
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch Watch
Po po po po po
Po po po po
Special song
What a special song
Then Dipsy heard
somebody else coming
Somebody coming
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch
lt was Tinky Winky
lt Tinky Winky
E-oh
Tinky Winky marched a clever march
Tinky Winky clever march
Dipsy watched
Dipsy watch
Tinky Winky clever march
What a clever march
Clever march
Dipsy loves Tinky Winky La-La and Po
Tinky Winky La-La Po
Big hug
Teletubbies love each other very much
Time for Tubby bye bye
time for Tubby bye bye
Noo No No
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye La La
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
Boo Boo
No No
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye La La
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye bye