Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One One
Two Two
Three Three
Four Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky Tinky Winky
Dipsy Dipsy
Laa-Laa Laa-Laa
Po Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Say hello
E oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Teletubbies
Big hug
Uh oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far a way
Oh what's that
What's that
It was a little lamb
Oh a little lamb
Oh little lamb ahh
Laa-Laa thought
the little lamb was sad
Oh little lamb is sad ahhh
So Laa-Laa did a dance
to make the little lamb happy
Laa-Laa do little dance
to make lamb happy
Little lamb
But the little lamb was still sad
Ahh little lamb is still sad ahh
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Oh what's that
It little lamb
Pardon
Little lamb
Oh little lamb
Tinky Winky thought
the little lamb was sad
Little lamb sad
Ahh
Tinky Winky thought the little lamb
wanted to be by the flowers
Little lamb by flowers
By flowers
Ahh
There
But the little lamb was still sad
Little lamb is sad
Ahh
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Laa-Laa
What's that
Little lamb ahh
Pardon
Oh little lamb ahh
Dipsy thought the little lamb was sad
Ah little lamb sad
Ahh
Dipsy thought the little lamb was sad
because it wanted to wear his hat
Little lamb Dipsy hat
But the little lamb was still sad
Little lamb sad
Ahh
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Oh what's that
Little lamb
Oh
Ahh
Little lamb
Po thought the little lamb was sad
Little lamb sad
Ahh
Po thought the little lamb was sad
because it wanted to ride her scooter
Little lamb scooter
Little lamb scooter little lamb scooter
But the little lamb was still sad
Ahh little lamb still sad ahh
Poor little lamb
Poor little lamb ahh
But then the Teletubbies heard a noise
What's that
The little lamb was happy
Little lamb happy
Bye bye lamb
All gone all gone all gone
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Eh-oh
Ohh
how now brown cow
Again again
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Look
What's that
how now brown cow
Pardon
Yes
Ohh
how now brown cow
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Look
Ohh what's that
how now brown cow
Pardon
Yes
Ohh
how now brown cow
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies were crawling
Crawling crawling crawling
Laa-Laa crawl
Tinky Winky crawl
Po crawl
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky crawled along the path
Along path
Tinky Winky crawl
Eh-oh
Dipsy crawled over the hill
Over the hill
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa crawled between the trees
Between the trees
Between trees
Eh-oh
Po crawled around the flowers
Po around flowers
Po crawl
After all that crawling
the Teletubbies were feeling very tired
Very tired very tired
So the Teletubbies crawled
all the way home
And into bed
lnto bed into bed
One day in Teletubbyland
a butterfly came
Ohh ahh ohh
Butterfly
Keep still Laa-Laa
Again again
Butterfly
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Shhh Dipsy look
Oh what's that
It's a butterfly
Butterfly
Ow
Get off
Urgh get off
Keep still Dipsy
Eh-oh
The butterfly landed on Po's scooter
Butterfly on Po's scooter
Where gone Where gone
Keep still Po
Pardon
Shh keep still Po
The butterfly land on Po head
Eh-oh
And then the butterfly went indoors
Ohh
Oh what's that
Look
Ahhh
Ahh uh-oh
Gone where gone
Bye bye butterfly
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Eh-oh
What's that
It was a dog
Dog
Dipsy patted the dog
Dipsy pat dog
Look
What a friendly dog
Friendly dog
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Look
Pardon Look
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Look
What's that
Dog
Pardon Dog
Dog Yes
Uh-oh
Look
Dog
Dog Dog
Dipsy and Tinky Winky
patted the dog
Dipsy pat dog
Tinky Winky pat dog
Ahhhhhh
What a friendly dog
Friendly dog
Ahhhhhh
And then the dog disappeared
Ooooh owwww
All gone all gone all gone
Eh-oh
Oooooohh
Woof woof woof
woof woof woof woof
Ohh
Woof woof woof
What's that
Woof What's that
Woof woof woof
Look
What's that
Woof woof woof
Again again
woof woof woof
Oww all gone all gone
All gone
Woof woof woof
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa Po
Oh
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye