Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy was feeling very tired
Very tired
Shhh
Soon Dipsy was fast asleep
Eh-oh
Outside Tinky Winky
Laa-Laa and Po were playing jumping
Jump jump
Oh it's so noisy so noisy noisy
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa
and Po had fallen asleep
Dipsy was asleep inside
And outside Tinky Winky
Laa-Laa and Po were asleep
All the Teletubbies were asleep
Peace peace peace at last
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
Uh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa was out for a walk when
she heard something very unusual
Oh what's that?
What's that?
Ohh
Laa-Laa looked at it but she had
never seen anything like it before
Laa-Laa never seen
anything like it before
Oh what's that?
It was a book
Oh book
And on the front of the book
was a picture of Laa-Laa
Picture of Laa-Laa!
Ohh picture of Laa-Laa
Open the book Laa-Laa
And on the first page was
a big picture of Teletubbyland
A picture of Teletubbyland look
Laa-Laa turned the page
And on the next page was a picture
of Teletubbyland with three rabbits
Oh rabbits
One two three
Three
Can you seen any rabbits
Ur no no rabbits
Laa-Laa turned the page
And on the next page was a picture of
a rabbit hopping out of a rabbit hole
Rabbit
Can you see a rabbit
hopping out of a rabbit hole?
There's one a rabbit
Rabbit
Rabbit rabbit
Laa-Laa turned the page
Laa-Laa turn the page
One
One rabbit
One rabbit one
Laa-Laa turned the page
Laa-Laa turn the page
On the next page was a picture of a
rabbit hopping out from behind a bush
Rabbit pop out behind the bush
Can you see a rabbit hopping
out from behind a bush?
There's one a rabbit hopping
out from behind a bush
Rabbit! Rabbit!
hop out behind the bush
Laa-Laa turned the page
Laa-Laa turn the page
Two
One two rabbits
Look!
Two rabbits
Two rabbits two
Laa-Laa turned the page
Laa-Laa turn the page
On the next page was a picture
of a rabbit hopping over a hill
The rabbit hop over the hill
Can you see a rabbit
hopping over the hill?
There's one! A rabbit
hopping over the hill
Rabbit! hopping over the hill
Laa-Laa turned the page
Three
One rabbit two rabbits three rabbits
Look
Laa-Laa turned the page
On the next page was a picture
of Laa-Laa and the rabbits
Oh Picture of Laa-Laa and the rabbits
Oh the rabbits rabbits
Laa-Laa and rabbits
The rabbits love Laa-Laa and
Laa-Laa loves rabbits very much
Laa-Laa love rabbits very much
One day in Teletubbyland Tinky Winky
woke up before the other Teletubbies
Eh-oh shhh
Tinky Winky was feeling very happy
Tinky Winky very happy
So Tinky Winky began to dance
Tinky Winky dance
Tinky Winky don't dance here
you'll wake up the other Teletubbies
So Tinky Winky went to dance outside
Tinky Winky dance outside
Eh-oh
What's that?
Oh What's that?
Eh-oh
It was Tinky Winky dancing
on top of the house
Tinky Winky on top of the house
Everybody danced
Everybody dance
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland it was time
for the Teletubbies to go to bed
Go to be go to be go to bed
Not tired
Tinky Winky Dipsy and
Laa-Laa were soon fast asleep
Fast asleep
But Po didn't want to go to sleep
Po wanted to ride her scooter
Scooter!
So while Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
were asleep Po rode her scooter
Po scooter
And then it was time for Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
Yee Dipsy toast
Tinky Winky toast
Po toast
Laa-Laa toast
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
The Teletubbies ate their Tubby Toast
Tinky Winky
Tubby Toast
Dipsy
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
And Laa-Laa
But Po was feeling too tired
to eat her Tubby Toast
Oh dear tired Po sleep
Po fell asleep
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Uh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy was asleep
Shhh Dipsy asleep
All the Teletubbies were
being very quiet
Dipsy asleep shh
Tinky Winky and Po were being quiet
Quiet shh
Uh-oh!
Dipsy sleep
Shh
Shh Dipsy asleep
Uh-oh! Shh Dipsy sleep
Shhh
Laa-Laa was being quiet
Laa-Laa being quiet
Shhh
Shhh Dipsy asleep
Uh-oh!
Dipsy sleep
Even Noo-Noo was being quiet
Noo-Noo shhh
Noo-Noo shh Dipsy sleep
Shh Dipsy sleep
And the Dipsy woke up
Eh-oh
Dipsy!
So Tinky Winky and Po
ate their Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
Laa-Laa played with her ball
Laa-Laa play ball
And the Noo-Noo cleaned up
Not very quietly
Shh shh
Dipsy!
Teletubbies love Dipsy
And Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug
Eh-oh
ltsy bitsy spider
Climbed up the water spout
Down came the rain
and washed the spider out
Again again
ltsy bitsy spider
Climbed up the water spout
Down came the rain
and washed the spider out
Ohh
Out came the sunshine
and dried up all the rain
So itsy bitsy spider
climbed up the spout again
Again again
ltsy bitsy spider
Climbed up the water spout
Down came the rain
and washed the spider out
ltsy bitsy spider
Out came the sunshine
and dried up all the rain
So itsy bitsy spider
climbed up the spout again
ltsy bitsy spider
Climbed up the water spout
Down came the rain
and washed the spider out
Out came the sunshine
and dried up all the rain
So itsy bitsy spider
climbed up the spout again
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Fr¨¨re Jacques Fr¨¨re Jacques
Dormez-vous dormez-vous
Sonnez les Matines
Ding dang dong
What's that?
Fr¨¨re Jacques Fr¨¨re Jacques
Dormez-vous dormez-vous
Sonnez les Matines
Ding dang dong
What's that?
Again again
Fr¨¨re Jacques Fr¨¨re Jacques
Dormez-vous dormez-vous
Sonnez les Matines
Ding dang dong
What's that what's that? What's that?
Again again
Shh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky was asleep in bed
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky sleep bed
Dipsy was asleep at the table
Dipsy asleep table
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa was asleep on the slide
Laa-Laa asleep on the slide
Eh-oh
And Po was asleep on her scooter
Po sleep scooter
Fancy riding a scooter
when you are asleep
ridiculous absolutely ridiculous
Then it was time for the
Teletubbies to wake up
Wake up Tinky Winky
Wake up!
Eh-oh
Wake up Dipsy
Wake up!
Eh-oh
Wake up Laa-Laa
Wake up!
Eh-oh
Wake up Po
Wake up!
Eh-oh
Wake up Po
Wake up Po!
Fancy riding a scooter
when you are asleep
how dangerous
how can she see where she is going
Wake up Po
Look
Look at that! Po is fast asleep in bed
Po asleep shh shh
Sleep well Po
Sleep well Teletubbies
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye