Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Eh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
lt was time for Ready Steady Go
Oooooohh! Ready Steady Go!
Ready Steady Go
Stretch up high
Stretch Up high
Stretch Up Stretch up
Stretch up high
Up high
Stretch Up high
Stretch Up Stretch up
Stretch up high
Up up up up up
Up & Down Up & Down Up & Down
Ready Steady Go
Up & Down
Up up up Down
Up Down
Big hug
Jumping he he he
Ready Steady Go
Jump jump jump jump
jump jump jump
Side To Side
Side to Side
Ready Steady Go
Side To Side
Side to Side
Stand Up Sit Down
Ready Steady Go
Stand up
Sit Down
Sit down
Stand up
Sit Down
Stand up Stand up
Sit down
Stand up Sit down
Stand up
Stand up Stand up
Sit Down
Sit down Sit down
Stand up Stand up
Sit Down
Sit down Sit down
Sit down
Big hug
Standing On One Leg
Ready Steady Go
Jolly good Look at that! Well done!
Very clever indeed
Standing On One Leg
Very good indeed Well done!
Bravo! Lovely! Ah Excellent!
Standing On One Leg
Other leg other leg
Ready Steady Go
Other leg
Look at that! Well done! Bravo!
Jumping Again
Ready steady go
Jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
the Teletubbies went for a walk
Oooohhh Walk
Ready steady go
Walk
The Teletubbies walked round
and round the flowers
Round The Flowers
Round & Round The Flowers
Round & Round
The Teletubbies walked sideways
Walk sideways
Walking sideways
walking sideways
Tinky Winky loves Marching
Marching
March March March
Tinky Winky Marching
March March
March March March March
March March March
Marching
Dipsy loves dancing
Dipsy Dancing
Dipsy Dance
Dancing Dancing Dance
Dancing
Dance Dipsy Dance Dipsy
Ray Dancing
Ray Big hug
Laa-Laa loves skipping
Skipping
LAA-LAA Skipping
Po loves crawling
Po Crawling
Crawling
And everybody loves jumping
Ready steady go
Jump jump jump
jump jump jump jump
Big hug
The Teletubbies were
feeling very tired
Very tired
So they decided to have a rest
Oooh rest
Ready steady go
Go to sleep Teletubbies
Go to sleep
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po