Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One One
Two Two
Three Three
Four Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky Tinky Winky
Dipsy Dipsy
Laa-Laa Laa-Laa
Po Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Say hello E oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Big hug
Uh oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone
E oh One day in Teletubbie Land
all the Teletubbies
were very very happy
Very very happy
Four happy Teletubbies
jumping round the tree
One jumped away
And then there were three
Oh
Ya yee sa
One two three
Three happy Teletubbies
What did they do
One went to hide
Oh aaah
Ooh where Dipsy gone
And then there were two
Ya yee
One two
Two happy Teletubbies out for a run
Faster and faster
And then there was one
Ya Oh dear tired Uh oh
One happy Teletubby lying in the sun
Rolled right away
And then there were none
Oooh oooh oooh
E oh
It was time for Tubbie toast
Tubbie toast tubbie toast yeah
tubbie toast
One Two Three Four
Yeah Tubbie toast
Uh oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Oook oook
hello hello
I am Joseph
come and meet my friends
hello hello
It's raining
Oh no we're going to get soaked
I like the rain because every time
it's raining
I watch out the window
I can't wait to go out
there to get wet
Would you wish you had
a rain sprinkler in your garden
Oh well only if I'd got a hood
Yeah
I need some help
I'll try
Try and help it cos
you've got to make it really click
I can't wait to get wet
I'm nearly ready Nearly ready
I'm ready
Well you haven't got your umbrella have you
No I've got my hat
We're going to use our umbrellas
Come on let's run
I'm getting all wet
My clothes are getting wet
Bye
One day in Teletubbie Land
a cloud appeared
and it began to rain
The cloud left something behind
What's that what's that
A big puddle
And do you know what happened
Uh oh
Eeerh
Dipsy trod in the puddle
Dipsy trod in the puddle eeerh
Uh oh
Mind the puddle Laa-Laa
Oooooh ooooh
Trog in de cruddle
Ooooh
Mind the puddle Tinky Winky
Pardon
What's that
Eeerh eeerh
Oh no
Uh oh
E oh
One day in Teletubbie Land
Tinky Winky was too full up
to finish his Tubbie toast
So he put it in his bag
to save it for later
ln bag
Tinky yeah
Bag
It wasn't very long
before Tinky Winky saw Dipsy's hat
hat
So he put it in his bag
hat in bag
A little further on
Tinky Winky saw Laa-Laa's ball
Laa-Laa's ball
So Tinky Winky put it in his bag
Ball in bag
Tinky Winky hadn't gone very far
when he saw Po's scooter
Po's scooter
So he put it in his bag
ln bag
There now Tinky Winky's bag was all full up
Tinky Winky's bag was rather heavy
Rather heavy
Tinky Winky couldn't carry it
Uh oh
Can you remember what's inside the bag
Well let's have a look
Uh oh
What's in the bag Tinky Winky
Po scooter
Po's scooter
Oh no
What else is in the bag
Uh oh
What's in the bag Tinky Winky
Laa-Laa's ball
What else
Uh oh
What's in the bag Tinky Winky
Dipsy's hat
No wonder the bag is so heavy Tinky Winky
Where hat
Where de ball
Where cooter
So Tinky Winky decided to take
everything out of the bag again
Scooter
Ball
hat
Yeah
Look hat hat
Ball ball
Cooter cooter
hat Ball Cooter
There now everybody's
got their favourite things
Uh oh
What's that noise
There's something
still in Tiny Winky's bag
Ooooh
Yum yum yum tubbie toast
Yeah tubbie toast
And Tinky Winky put the piece of
tubbie toast back in his bag
to save it for later
Oh
One day in Teletubbie Land
Po fell out of bed
Oh dear
She fell down from the table
Uh oh
She fell over from surprise
Oh dear
Po Laa-Laa
Big hug
Tinky Winky was watching the rabbits
when Po fell off her scooter
Oh dear
Uh oh Po fell off her cooter
And Tinky Winky fell over
Laa-Laa came to help
E oh Whoops
And Laa-Laa fell over
Dipsy came to help
E oh Uh oh
Oh dear
now all the Teletubbies have fallen over
E oh
Uh oh
One day in Teletubbie Land
Tinky Winky saw that somebody had spilled
their Tubbie custard on the floor
Somebody pilled the Tubbie custard Uh oh
But whoever it was had left footprints
Who spilled the Tubbie custard
Who pilled the Tubbie custard
Oooh
Tinky Winky followed the footprints
Footprints
over the hills
Over the hills
And around the bush
Around the bush
To the place where
Dipsy was sitting with the rabbits
E oh Dipsy
E oh Tinky Winky
Was it Dipsy who spilled the custard
Dipsy pill the Tubbie custard
No No
And sure enough the footprints carried on
Who spilled the Tubbie custard
Who pilled the Tubbie custard
Tinky Winky and Dipsy followed
the footprints over the hills
Over the hills
To the place where Laa-Laa was dancing
E oh Laa-Laa
E oh Dipsy e oh Tinky Winky
Was it Laa-Laa
who spilled the Tubbie custard
Laa-Laa pilled the Tubbie custard
No
And sure enough the footprints
carried on
Who spilled the Tubbie custard
Who pilled the Tubbie custard
Who
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
followed the footprints over the hills
Over the hills
ln and out of the trees
Across the path
Around the house
And then they went indoors
They went indoors lndoors indoors
To the place
where Po was fast asleep
Uh oh
Was it Po
who spilled the Tubbie custard
Who spilled the Tubbie custard
Po
One day in Teletubbie Land
something appeared
E oh Oh what s that what s that
Ooh what s that what s that
It was a watering can
E oh
Lovely water lovely water
One day in Teletubbie Land
Laa-Laa found a watering can
Oooh
One day in the Teletubbie Land
Laa-Laa found a watering can
Mary Mary quite contrary
how does your garden grow
With silver bells and cockle shells
And pretty maids all in a row
Oooh again again nice
Mary Mary quite contrary
how does your garden grow
With silver bells and cockle shells
And pretty maids all in a row
E oh
One day in Teletubbie Land
Laa-Laa felt like having
some Tubbie toast
Yeah Laa-Laa feel like habing
de Tubbie Toast Tubbie toast
Tubbie toast
Yeah the Tubbie toast tubbie
Yeah the Tubbie toast
tubbie toast
Yeah yeah de Tubbie toast
Tubbie toast
Yeah Tubbie toast
Laa-Laa smelled her Tubbie toast
It smelled delicious
Delicious
E oh
Tinky Winky was out for a walk
when Tinky Winky smelled
Tubbie toast as well
Tubbie toast Tubbie toast
It smelled delicious
Oh delicious
So Tinky Winky decided to go
and have some Tubbie toast as well
E oh Laa-Laa
E oh Tinky Winky
Tubbie toast Tubbie toast
Yeah de Tubbie toast
Yeah Tubbie toast Tubbie toast
Oh where de Tubbie toast
Where the Tubbie toast
Oh Tubbie toast
Tubbie toast Tubbie toast
Uh oh
Where the Tubbie toast
Oh Tubbie toast
Oh look Tubbie toast
Oh look Tubbie toast Tubbie toast
Oh
Uh oh
Oh dear
There was Tubbie toast
all over the table
Oh dear be Tubbie toast
all over tde table Oh no
There was Tubbie toast
all over the floor
all over the beds
Tubbie toast all over de bed
Oh dear Oh my my
And there was Tubbie toast
all over Tinky Winky
De Tubbie toast all over
Tinky Winky Oh dear
There was Tubbie toast everywhere
Everywhere
Tubbie toast everywhere
There was lots of Tubbie toast
for Noo Noo
And lots of Tubbie toast for Po
Lots of Tubbie toast for Po
And lots of Tubbie toast
for Laa-Laa
Lots of de Tubbie toast for Laa-Laa
And lots of Tubbie toast for Dipsy
Tubbie toast for Dipsy
And lots of Tubbie toast
for Tinky Winky
Tubbie toast for Tinky Winky
And lots of Tubbie toast
for the rabbits
or everybody
Yeah de Tubbie toast for everybody
Uh oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Oh Tinky Winky
hello
E oh
Children playing on the beach
with ball and dog
where's the ball gone
Jezza where's the ball
It's gone
Jezza Jezza
Jezza
Where's the ball gone
I don't know
Got to find it
Jezza Jezza Jezza
Jezza's got the ball
Jezza's found the ball
There it is
Bye bye
One day in Teletubbie Land
Dipsy was out for a walk
when do you know what happened
No
Oh no
The wind blew Dipsy's hat away
Oh no the wind blew
Dipsy's hat away
Where's my hat said Dipsy
Where's my hat
Po was on her scooter
Whee
Where's my hat said Dipsy
Where's my hat
Uh oh
Ah
Tinky Winky was very surprised
to see Dipsy's hat
Ah Dipsy's hat oh Dipsy's hat
Tinky Winky was very surprised
to see Dipsy s hat
Dipsy's hat Oh Dipsy's hat
Laa-Laa came out
to see what was going on
What's going on
Oooh
E oh Tinky Winky
E oh Laa-Laa
Look Dipsy's hat
Laa-Laa went to find Dipsy
Dipsy Dipsy
Where's my hat where's my hat
Dipsy
Where's my hat Dipsy
hat hat hat Dipsy
Dipsy hat Dipsy hat
Dipsy hat
Dipsy
Teletubbies love each other very much
Time for Tubbie bye bye
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye Laa-Laa
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
Boo Boo
No
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye Laa-Laa
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye bye