Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day from Teletubbyland
something appeared in the hills
Eh oh
Tinky Winky thought
he heard something
Oh what's that?
Eh oh
Ohh what's that?
What's that?
Eh oh
Laa-Laa heard it
Oh what's that?
Eh oh
And Po heard it
Oh What's that?
What's that?
And they all went
to see what it was
What's that?
Ohhhh
It was a Christmas tree
Christmas tree
Ohhh
The Teletubbies had never seen
a Christmas tree before
Never seen Christmas tree before
Ohhh
Ohhh, look
One, two, three, four presents
One, two, three, four presents!
One present for Laa-Laa
Present for Laa-Laa
Ohh the present for Laa-Laa
One present for Po
Oh present for Po
One present for Dipsy
Yes
And one present for Tinky Winky
Ohh
Present for Tinky Winky
hooray
The Teletubbies loved
their presents very much
Presents! Presents!
And the Teletubbies
love each other very much
Big hug
Eh oh
Look!
Ohh
What's that?
Ohh owww
Uh oh!
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa had a present
Laa-Laa present
Ohh, the present
present, present, present
Eh oh
Present, present
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Po
Laa-Laa present
Ohh
Present! Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa present
Laa-Laa decided to open her present
Ohh, Laa-Laa open the present
Ohh, what's that?
Decorations
Laa-Laa was very pleased
with her present
Laa-Laa very pleased with present
So she decided to
show the other Teletubbies
Show the other Teletubbies
Tinky Winky!
Dipsy!
Po!
Eh oh
Eh oh, Po
Eh oh, Dipsy
Eh oh, Tinky Winky
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Look!
Oh what's that?
Decorations
Ohhh
But then the Noo-Noo
decided to tidy up
Ahhh
Uh oh!
Owww
Oww
Oh no
Naughty Noo-Noo
Naughty Noo-Noo!
All those decorations felt
rather tickly inside the Noo-Noo
Ohh, ahh, ohh
Look, decorations
Look
how festive
The Teletubbies love the Noo-Noo
And the Teletubbies
love each other very much
Big hug
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Po had a present
Ohh ahh
Po, present, look, look
Po, present
Ohh
Eh oh
Laa-Laa saw that
Po had left her present behind
Ohh
Look
Po left the present! Uh oh!
Po! Po! Po!
Po! Po! Po
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Po
Look left the present
Uh oh!
Po was very happy to
have her present back
Po very happy with the present
Yes
Big hug
Present
What's that?
Ohh
Po decided to open the present
Po open present
Open up the present
What's that?
It was a little frosty cloud
Ohh ahh
Little frosty cloud
And the little frosty
cloud began top snow
Snow
What's that?
Little frosty cloud snow
Snow
Look, snow
Snow! Snow! Snow!
Tinky Winky and Dipsy
came to see the snow
Eh oh
Eh oh, Po
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Tinky Winky
Eh oh, Dipsy
Look
Ohh what's that?
Snow
Teletubbies love snow
And Teletubbies
love each other very much
Big hug
Uh oh!
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy had a present
Ohh, present, present
Dipsy got a present
Ohh, present
Dipsy decided to open his present
Present, present, open the present
What's that?
Cracker!
Cracker, cracker, cracker
Dipsy got a cracker
Dipsy was very pleased
with his present
Cracker, cracker, cracker
Dipsy got a cracker
Cracker cracker cracker
Dipsy looked for someone
to help pull the cracker
Pull cracker
Eh oh
Laa-Laa! Laa-Laa!
Look
Dipsy, what's that?
Cracker
Cracker?
Yes
Ohh
Cracker, cracker, cracker
Dipsy got a cracker
Dipsy asked Laa-Laa
to help him pull the cracker
Laa-Laa help Dipsy
Yes
Dipsy and Laa-Laa pulled
as hard as they could
But Dipsy and Laa-Laa were not strong
enough to pull the cracker
Dipsy and Laa-Laa not strong enough
So they looked for
someone else to help
Eh oh
Oh, Tinky Winky
Yes
Look
Dipsy and Laa-Laa asked Tinky Winky
if he would help pull the cracker
Tinky Winky help pull the cracker
Yes
hooray
Dipsy and Laa-Laa and Tinky Winky
pulled as hard as they could
Again, again
Pull! Pull
But Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
were not strong enough
to pull the crackers
So they looked for
someone else to help
Eh oh
Eh oh, Tinky Winky
Eh oh, Dipsy
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Po
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa asked Po
if she would help them
pull the cracker
Po help pull cracker?
Yes
hooray
Dipsy and Laa-Laa and Tinky Winky
and Po pulled as hard as they could
Pull, pull, pull, pull
Again, again
Pull, pull, pull
And do you know what happened?
No
Teletubbies love
the cracker very much
the crackervery much
Teletubbies love
the cracker very much
And Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy was making some adjustments
Eh oh
Some adjustments
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky had a present
Oh, look
Tinky Winky present
Look!
Ohh
Tinky Winky present
Tinky Winky opened the present
Tinky Winky open present
Ahh
What's that?
Ohh ahh
It was a star
Star, ohh
Tinky Winky wondered
where the star was going
Where star going
Tinky Winky followed the star
Follow star
Oh what's that?
Eh oh, Tinky Winky
Eh oh, Po
What's that?
Star
Po wondered
where the star was going
Where star going
So Tinky Winky and Po
followed the star
Follow star
Eh oh
What's that?
Oh look
Eh oh, Dipsy
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Po
Eh oh, Dipsy
Eh oh, Laa-Laa
Eh oh, Tinky Winky
Look
Star
Laa-Laa and Dipsy wondered
where the star was going
Where star going
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa and Po
followed the star
Follow the star
Tinky Winky Po Laa-Laa and Dipsy
followed the star
all the way
to the Christmas tree
happy Christmas Teletubbies
Big hug
happy Christmas, Teletubbies
Time for Tubby
Bye-bye
time for Tubby
Oh. Oh. Oh, no!
Bye-bye, Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye, Dipsy
Bye-bye, Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye, Po
Boo!
Boo, he, he, he
No
Bye-bye, Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye, Dipsy
Bye-bye, Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye, Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye