Eh-oh
Teletubbies everywhere
Eh-oh Eh-oh Eh-oh Eh-oh
Pink
Eh-oh
Look! Ohhhh what's that?
Pink
Pink! Pink pink pink pink
Eh-oh!
Yeee!
hooray!
Ohhhh yeee! Dipsy!
Square
Eh-oh
Near
Oh near near
hooray! Eh-oh
Far
Far! Far! hooray
Bye-bye
Eh-oh
Yee the Laa-Laa
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
Bye-bye
Eh-oh
Teletubbies everywhere
Eh-oh Eh-oh Eh-oh Eh-oh
Eh-oh
One Po
Two Pos
Three Pos
Eh-oh
Two Pos
One Po
Bye-bye
Purple
Eh-oh
Oh Purple hey!
Purple
Eh-oh
Jumping
Jumping!
Bye-bye
Eh-oh
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
Bye-bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Oh Oh oh
Eh-oh
Oh what's that?
It was a mirror
Mirror
What's that?
Laa-Laa saw her reflection in the mirror
Flextion
Laa-Laa!
One arm
Two arms
Look
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa liked looking at her reflection
in the mirror
Laa-Laa liked looking at flection in mirror
One arm
Two arms
One leg
The other leg
Other leg
Mirror!
One arms two arms one leg other leg
Silly how silly
One arm two arms one leg other leg
Laa-Laa liked looking at her reflection
in the mirror
What's that?
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Look!
What's that?
lt's a mirror
Pardon
Mirror?
Yes
Look Look mirror
Mirror
here are here are
Look
Dipsy and Tinky Winky saw their reflection
in the mirror
Flection
Eh-oh
Dipsy and Tinky Winky liked looking at
their reflection in the mirror
Like flection in mirror
Eh-oh
Oh Po
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
What's that?
Mirror
Oh mirror
Po looked in the mirror
Oh Po look mirror
Po saw her reflection in the mirror
Oh Po flection
Po flection
Po liked looking at her reflection
in the mirror
Po liked looking at her flection in mirror
Po flection
But not as much as she liked
to ride her scooter
'Cooter
Bye-bye Po
And then the mirror disappeared
Ohhhh all gone
All gone
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
Eh-Oh Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Po
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
went where Laa-Laa was
Where Laa-Laa? Where Laa-Laa
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
went looking for Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po thought
Laa-Laa might be in the house
Laa-Laa! Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
But Laa-Laa wasn't in the house
Laa-Laa not in the house
So Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
went looking for Laa-Laa again
Laa-Laa look for Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa Laa-Laa
Po thought that Laa-Laa might be
just over the hill
Over hill
So Po went over the hill to see
Po see
Laa-Laa!
Yes
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Po
Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Teletubbies love Laa-Laa
Big hug
and Teletubbies love each other very much
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland it was time for
Dipsy to make some adjustments
Justments
Justments justments justments
Dipsy adjusted the levers
Dipsy just levers
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa Po
Yes
Look Dipsy adjust levers
Uh-oh!
Don't pull that lever Dipsy
Don't pull the lever Dipsy
Again Again
Again again
Uh-oh!
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye