Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Say hello
Uh oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy
La La Po
Teletubbies
Big hug
Uh oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone
Big hug
Eh oh Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland something
appeared from far away
Eh oh
Oh Ooh what's that
What's that
It was a door
Oh a door Oh
Po opened the door
Po open door
Po went through the door
Po through door
Po shut the door
Po shut door
Eh oh!
Oh look What's that
La La saw the door
Oh door Eee door eee
La La knocked on the door
Oh La La knock on the door
La La knock on the door
One two three
And Po answered the door
Ooh
Eh oh La La
Eh oh Po hee hee
Big hug
La La and Po went through the door
La La and Po through the door
La La and Po shut the door
Ooh La La and Po shut door
Shut the door Shut the door
Bye-bye Bye-bye
Eh oh
Oh what's that?
what's that?
Ah what's that?
Dipsy saw the door
Oh door door
Dipsy knocked on the door
Oh Dipsy knock door
Dipsy knock door
One two three
And La La and Po answered the door
Eh oh Dipsy
Eh oh Po Eh oh La La
Big hug Big hug
Dipsy and La La and Po
went through the door
Dipsy and La La and Po through the door
Dipsy and La La and Po shut the door
Oh Dipsy and La La and Po
shut the door shut the door
bye-bye
Eh oh
Oh look
Oh What's that?
What's that?
Tinky Winky saw the door
Door Door
Tinky Winky knocked on the door
Tinky Winky knock at door
One two three
And Dipsy La La and Po
answered the door
Eh oh Tinky Winky
Eh oh Dipsy Eh oh La La Eh oh Po
Big hug Big hug
Tinky Winky Dipsy La La
and Po went through the door
and Po go through the door
Tinky Winky Dipsy
La La and Po go through the door
La La and Po shut the door
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Shut the door shut the door
Bye-bye bye-bye
And then the door disappeared
Oh bye-bye bye-bye
Big hug
La la la la la Eh oh
Eh oh Po
Eh oh La La
Big hug
Eh oh
Uh oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Oohh Aah oh ahh
hello hello hello hello
Uh oh
hello my name's Jack
hello my name's Francesca
Let's find Andy
hello Andy hello Andy
hello Francesca hello Jack
Are you going to help me
look for some rabbits
Yes
We're going to look for some rabbits
come on
shall we look over there
Looking for rabbits
I think there must
be a rabbit round here
look how short the grass is
Yeah Must be a rabbit
I know where the rabbits are
Where are they?
ln here in the sand
Oh look here
See that's hole there
That's a rabbit hole isn't it?
Yeah
Oh do you see what there is here though
That's rabbit droppings
There must be loads of holes under here
Mmm
how many rabbits
do you think there'll be?
Ten
hundreds
hundreds there could be hundreds
Look at that one another one there
Are there there
Can you see anything
No
We can see a warren here
Yeah it's a big warren isn't it?
A warren
A big family of rabbits all
living in their little burrows
We'll hide in here
Look I've got some binoculars for you
so you can see it properly
These will help you see the rabbits
Thank you Let's try to find a rabbit
See if you can see it see that rabbit
Can you see any
Look there did you see that one
Coming out of the hole up there
Yeah
Did you see that?
You look Jack Jack Look up by that hole
What's he doing?
Rabbits love to eat the grass
That one's eating the flowers
What's he doing?
Lovely rabbit
They're always eating
rabbit Goodbye rabbit
Bye-bye everybody bye-bye bye-bye
Tinky Winky Tinky Winky
ha ha ha B ba ba boom
Whey
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland the
Teletubbies were feeling very happy
hey very happy very happy
And it was time for Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast Tubby Toast Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast Tubby Toast
Big hug Big hug
Big hug
And it was time for Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast
Oh Tubby toast Tubby toast
Big hug
Tubby Toast Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast
Eh Dipsy Toast
hey Tinky Winky toast
Po Toast Po Toast
La La toast
Tubby Toast Tubby Toast
Big hug Big hug Big hug
Tubby Toast
Ah mmm yum mmm
Look at that the Tubby table is
covered in Tubby toast crumbs
Ooh oh
Oh noo noo
Yees
There that's better
That's better That's better
Ah I give big hug
Ah I give noo noo big hug
hey hey noo noo noo noo
coming noo noon
The Teletubbies love the noo noo
Aah Aah
And the Teletubbies
love each other very much
Aah Aah big hug big hug
Uh oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
hey La La
hello hello hello hello
Eh oh
Come and see Tamzin play Funny Lady
Knock Knock
Oh yes do come in Do come in
Do come in please Very good
Now I'm going to do funny lady Brrrrrr
Today is King and Queen day
And we're all in green
Teddy is the King and I am the Queen
Teddy had a crown and I had one too
Where is my crown?
Where can she be?
I hope she comes soon
because it's nearly time for tea
Crown crown where are you
Crown crown are you up are you down
Well where can she be
it's nearly time for tea
There it's swinging
I am a crown and I don't bend down
I sit high and I sit proud
near the sky and the cloud
and I sit all day in a very crowny way
Thank you very much goodbye
Crown
Well what a naughty proud crown
Oh where can she be
I hope she comes soon
because it's nearly time for tea
Crown crown where are you?
Crown crown are you up are you down
Oh where oh where can she be
because it's nearly time
for tea and biscuits
I am a crown and I don't bend down
I sit high I sit proud
near the sky and the cloud
And I sit all day in a very crowny way
Thank you very much goodbye
Now what a naughty proud crown
Oh where oh where can she be
I hope she comes soon
because it's nearly time for tea
Crown crown Where are you?
Crown crown are you up and down
Oh where oh where oh where can she be?
I hope she comes soon
because it's nearly time
for tea and biscuit and cake
Cake cake
And cake
She's got to come now
Cake
Well what are we going to do King Teddy?
What was that Teddy?
Crown needs her special
invitation just like mine Oh
so the Crown needs a special
invitation like this one
I know just the place to look
Let's look in my handbag
Da di da da di da
here it is
The Crown's special invitation
Shall we call her again?
Yes
Crown Crown where are you?
Crown crown are you up are you down
Crown crown We've got something
very special for you
Oh where oh where oh where can she be
I hope she comes soon
because it's nearly time for tea
and biscuits and cake and icecream
I am a crown and I don't bend down
I sit high I sit proud near
the sky and the cloud
I sit all day in a very crowny way
Thank you very much hello
Well what a very proud crown
As proud as can be
Everybody's happy
and now it's time for tea
Tea
One cup
Two cups three cups four cups
There's some for you some for you
Do you want one there we are
tea time
Now who wants some biscuits
Yes Yes
Biscuit Biscuit
Mmm delicious biscuit
Yum yum yum yum yum
Now we've had a lovely tea
and a lovely biscuit
It's time to say goodbye
Bye bye Bye bye bye
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland
La La invited Dipsy to go
for a walk over the hills
Ah oh oh
Dipsy
Yes
Shall we go for a walk over hills
Dipsy go for walk on the hills
Eer er yes
Ahh hee hee
And Dipsy was pleased to accept
Yes Yes
hey
One day in Teletubby Dipsy invited
La La to walk all the way home again
La La home
Again
Oh yes please Dipsy
And La La was pleased to accept
Yes
La La La La La La
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug big hug hey
Eh oh
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Oh what's that
It was a magic cloud
Ooh magic cloud
The magic cloud began
to rain magic rain
Magic cloud with magic powers
raining special magic showers
Planting little magic flowers
Oh magic flowers Oh
Aah ahh
Po thought the magic flowers
smelled lovely
Ahh smell lovely Ahh ahh
The magic cloud rained on PO's scooter
Magic cloud with magic powers
raining little magic showers
making little magic flowers
Ooh
Ooh scooter magic flowers Aah
Po thought her scooter smelled lovely
Scooter smell lovely Ahh
Eh oh
The magic cloud rained on La La's ball
Magic cloud with magic powers
raining special magic showers
planting little magic flowers
magic flowers
La La thought her ball smelled lovely
Ooh ball smell lovely
Oh Ah ah Mmm
Ball smell lovely Oh
Uh oh
The magic cloud rained on Tinky Winky
Magic cloud with magic powers
raining special magic showers
and planting little magic flowers
Oh magic flowers
Tinky Winky thought he smelled lovely
Ahh Tinky Winky smell lovely
Eh oh
Uh oh
Magic cloud with magic powers
raining special magic showers
planting special magic flowers
Eh oh
Dipsy thought his hat smelled lovely
Eeh Eeh Oh no
Eeh eeh eeh eeh
La la la la la la la la la
Oh Eh Oh
One day in Teletubbyland
La La decided to give all the other
Teletubbies a big hug
Oh a big hug a big hug
Ahh hug
Big hug big hug Oh
Eh oh
First of all La La gave Po a big hug
La la la la la la Eh oh Po
Eh oh La La Ahh ahh
Again again
Bye-bye Bye-bye
hey Again again Ahh Ahh
Eh oh
La la la la la la la la
La La gave Dipsy a big hug
Oh Dipsy big hug
Dipsy Dipsy Dipsy Dipsy
Dipsy Dipsy
La La La La
Dipsy La La
Dipsy big hug
Ahh Big hug
Bye-bye Bye-bye
La La La La La La
Dipsy
Again Again again
Again again
Ahh Bye-bye
Next La La gave Tinky Winky a big hug
Oh next is Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky
Where is Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky all gone
Tinky Winky
Eh oh La La
Tinky Winky Ahh
Bye-bye Aah again
hug hug Again again
Ahh ahh
Teletubbies love each other very much
Ahh ahh Big hug
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh ahh No no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye La La
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo Oh eh
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye La La
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye