Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland the
Teletubbies were feeling very happy
Very happy very happy
feeling very happy
Oh dear what a mess!
It was time for Tinky Winky
and Dipsy to have Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
Oh dear what a mess!
Uh-oh
Eh-oh
It was time for Laa-Laa
and Po to have Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
Uh-oh
Ohh
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
Oh dear what a mess!
Oh dear Uh-uh
What a lot of mess!
The Tubby beds were in a mess
The Tubby Custard machine
was in a mess
And the Tubby table was in a mess
Uh-oh oh dear
And so the Noo-Noo tidied up
Ahh Noo-Noo tidy up
Noo-Noo tidied up the beds
Noo-Noo tidy beds
There all tidy
Noo-Noo tidied up the
Tubby Custard machine
There all tidy
Then Noo-Noo tidied up the Tubby table
The Noo-Noo tidy up
There all tidy
Clever Noo-Noo
Ahh Thank you Noo-Noo
Ahh Noo-Noo
Uh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland something
appeared from far away
Oh look at that look at that
What's that?
It was a ball of string
Oh string
Tinky Winky pulled the string
Tinky Winky pull the string
Pull string
Tinky Winky pulled and pulled
Tinky Winky pull and pull
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky showed Laa-Laa the string
Laa-Laa
Yes Tinky Winky
Look
Oh what's that?
pardon
What's that?
String
Pardon
Ohh
Ohh ohh string
Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa
pulled the string
Pull the string pull pull
Eh-oh
Oh What's that?
It was string
Oh string
Dipsy trod on the string
Uh-oh
Oh dear
The string stopped
String stop
Ohh
Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa
didn't know why the
string had stopped
Don't know why why string stopped why
So Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa followed
the string to see
Follow string follow string
Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa
followed the string over the hills
Over the hills
Eh-oh
Dipsy!
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Dipsy
Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa saw Dipsy
standing on the string
Oh Dipsy on the string
Dipsy step on string
Po was going very fast on her scooter
Uh-oh
Mind the ball of string Po
Mind the string Po
Pardon
Uh-oh
Teletubbyland was
all covered in string
heee
What a stringy mess!
Stringy mess
The Noo-Noo tidies up
Noo-Noo tidy up hooray
Clever Noo-Noo
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
But then Dipsy had an accident
Uh-oh accident uh oh
Uh-oh
Dipsy spilled Tubby Custard
all over his Tubby seat
Dipsy spill custard look Uh-oh
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and
Po sat down on their Tubby seats
but Dipsy didn't want to sit down
Dipsy don't want to sit down urghhhh
Dipsy didn't want to
sit in the Tubby Custard
Dipsy not sit in the
Tubby Custard urghhhh
Urghhh
Dipsy had nowhere to sit
Dipsy nowhere to sit
So Laa-Laa let Dipsy
sit on her Tubby seat
here are Dipsy
Thank you Laa-Laa
Then Laa-Laa had nowhere to sit
Uh-oh Laa-Laa nowhere to sit
Uh-oh
Laa-Laa didn't want to
sit in the Tubby Custard
Laa-Laa don't want to
sit in the Tubby Custard urghhh
Urghhh
So Po let Laa-Laa
sit on her Tubby seat
here are Laa-Laa
Thank you Po
But then Po had nowhere to sit
Uh-oh
Uh-oh nowhere to sit
Po didn't want to sit
in the Tubby Custard
Urghhh
So Tinky Winky let Po sit on his seat
Uh-oh
here are Po
Thank you Tinky Winky
But then Tinky Winky
had nowhere to sit
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky didn't want to sit
in the Tubby Custard
Urghhh
Dipsy and Laa-Laa
both wanted to let Tinky Winky
sit down on their Tubby seats
here are Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky couldn't decided
which seat to sit on
Uh-oh
here are Tinky Winky
But then Laa-Laa and
Dipsy wanted to sit down
Laa-Laa and Dipsy
wanted to sit down
here are Dipsy here are Laa-Laa
Oh Dipsy
Laa-Laa had nowhere to sit
Laa-Laa nowhere to sit
Laa-Laa didn't want to
sit in the Tubby Custard
Laa-Laa no want to sit
in the Tubby Custard
urghhh
So Laa-Laa sang a song
The Noo-Noo tidied up
Noo-Noo tidied up
Yeee Noo-Noo
Laa-Laa had somewhere to sit
Somewhere to sit
All the Teletubbies were sitting down
But the Teletubbies were sitting down
in the wrong places
Wrong places Uh oh
So they changed places
Change places
There
And then it was time
to eat Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard Tubby Custard
Uh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
the Teletubbies were watching
the clouds float by
Clouds float by
A big fluffy one floated by
A big fluffy one
A long thin wispy one floated by
Long thin wispy one
A little puffy one floated by
Little puffy one?
And do you know what happened?
The little puffy cloud floated indoors
Uh-oh
Ahhhhh
It was time for Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard
Tubby tustard
The Tubbies found it rather inconvenient
having a cloud indoors
lnconvenient
Uh-oh
The Noo-Noo came to
tidy up the custard
The Noo-Noo tidy up the custard
Aaaah The Noo-Noo tidy up the custard
Ooooh
Thank you Noo-Noo
The Noo-Noo began to tidy up the cloud
But all that custard and all that cloud
were getting very
mixed up inside Noo-Noo
Uh-oh
Bye-bye special pink
Tubby Custard cloud
Bye-bye
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo he he he Boo he he he
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Bye-bye
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye