Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
Again again
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky danced
the Boom Boom Dance
Tinky Winky Boom Boom Dance
Eh-oh
Dipsy danced the Boom Boom Dance
Dipsy Boom Boom Dance
Boom boom
That's very good lovely dancing
lovely dancing very good
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa danced the Boom Boom Dance
Laa-Laa dance the Boom Boom Dance
Laa-Laa dance the Boom Boom
Eh-oh
Po danced the Boom Boom Dance
Po Boom Boom dance
Boom Boom dance
All the Teletubbies
danced the Boom Boom Dance
Boom Boom Dance
Teletubbies love
the Boom Boom Dance
Teletubbies love Boom Boom Dance
And the Teletubbies
love each other very much
Big hug
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky sang a song about the bag
Tinky Winky song bag
Bag
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy sang a song about the hat
Dipsy song hat
ha-at ha-at ha-at ha-at ha-at
Oh hat
hat hat
Eh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa sang a song about the ball
Ohh Laa-Laa sing a song the ball
Ball ball ball ball
ball ball ball
Ball!
Eh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
Po sang a song about a cloud
Po song cloud
Cloud cloud cloud
cloud cloud cloud
Cloud!
Cloud cloud cloud cloud
Cloud
Urghh
Run away! Run away!
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
What are those? What are they?
Eh-oh
Ohh what's that?
lt was a pair of mittens
Mittens
Tinky Winky put the mittens on
Mittens on
Uh-oh
No Tinky Winky
you don't wear mittens on your ears
You don't wear mittens on your ears
everybody knows that
There Eh-oh
No Tinky Winky
you don't wear mittens on your knees
Uh-oh
lt is ridiculous
mittens on knees silly
Eh-oh there there
That's right Tinky Winky
mittens go on your hands
hooray mittens on hands
That's better at last at last
Tinky Winky liked wearing
mittens on his hands
Mittens on hands
So Tinky Winky did a special dance
with the mittens
Special dance mittens
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky showed Po the mittens
Show Po mittens
Po look
What's that?
Mittens
Mittens?
Tinky Winky showed Po
his special dance with the mittens
Show Po dance
Ohh
lt was Po's turn
to wear the mittens on her hands
Po mittens
Mittens
So Po did a special dance
with the mittens
Po dance mittens
Po mittens
Then the mittens disappeared
Uh-oh
Look
All gone
Big hug
Big hug Noo-noo
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
the Teletubbies were sitting
at the table listening to music
Ohh the Teletubbies
listen to music
Listen music listen
Ohhh
What lovely music
Lovely music
lovely music lovely music
Again again
Shhhh Noo-noo shhh
Noo-noo shhh Noo-noo shhh
What lovely music
Again again
Noo-noo! Shh Noo-noo!
Shhh Noo-noo shh
Noo-noo shhhh
What lovely music
Lovely music
Again
Again again
Noo-noo shhh Noo-noo shhh
Ohhh where the music
music all gone all gone
oh dear all gone
Ahh Noo-noo
What lovely music
Lovely music
Noo-noo!
The Teletubbies love the Noo-noo
Love the Noo-noo
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Eh-oh
Ohh look
what's that?
lt was a harp
harp
Tinky Winky played the harp
Tinky Winky play harp
Again again
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Look
What's that?
Oh what's that?
harp
Pardon
Yes
Look
Yee
Ohhh
Po played the harp
Po play harp
And then the harp disappeared
Bye bye harp
All gone
Big hug
Teletubbies love each other
very much
Big hug
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye