Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Eh-oh
Ohh what's that?
What's that?
Oh What's that?
It was a fountain
Fountain
Laa-Laa thought
the fountain was very pretty
Very pretty
It made Laa-Laa want
to sing a fountain song
Laa-Laa sing song
What a very pretty song
A very pretty song
Laa-Laa sang her fountain song high
Laa-Laa sing song high
Laa-Laa sang her fountain song low
Laa-Laa sing song low
Then Laa-Laa sang
her fountain song high and low
Laa-Laa sing song high and low
What a very pretty song
Very pretty song
And what a very pretty fountain
Very pretty fountain
And then the fountain disappeared
Oww no
All gone all gone
Eh-oh
Ohh
Oh
Dipsy Dipsy look!
Look Laa-Laa
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Eh-oh
Oh what's that?
What's that?
It was a carpet
Carpet
What a lovely carpet
Lovely carpet
Tinky Winky wanted
to walk on the carpet
Tinky Winky walk carpet
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky walk carpet uh-oh
Tinky Winky liked
walking on the carpet
Tinky Winky walk carpet
Oh dear! Look at that
Tinky Winky's feet
have made dirty marks on the carpet
Uh-oh!
Oh dear now the carpet is all dirty
All dirty
What a dirty carpet
Dirty carpet Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky knew just what to do
he sang a special song
Tinky Winky special song
The carpet was all clean
All clean
What a clean carpet
Clean carpet
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Look
Eh-oh Dipsy
What's that?
Carpet
Pardon
Oh carpet
Dipsy wanted to
walk on the carpet
Dipsy walk carpet
Look at that!
Dipsy's feet are all dirty
Dipsy feet dirty
Dipsy you can't walk
on the carpet with dirty feet
You'll make dirty marks
Uh-oh!
Dipsy carpet
Dipsy carpet!
Uh-oh!
Dipsy carpet
Oh no!
Uh-oh!
Oh dear
And then the carpet disappeared
Ohh all gone
all gone all gone
Big hug
Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
It was a box
but this was no ordinary box
What's in the box?
helloooo
Jack in the box
Eh-oh
Oh what's that?
Ohh
What's that?
It was a box
Box
But this was no ordinary box
No ordinary box
What's in the box?
hellooooo
A Jack in the box
A Jack in a box
Oh no! Oh dear
Laa-Laa thought
the Jack in a box was very surprising
Very surprising
Oh all gone all gone all gone
Jack in the box
Jack in the box!
Ohh
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Look
Oh what's that?
What's that?
It was a box
It box
Oh box
Box
But this was no ordinary box
This is no ordinary box
Ohh
What's in the box?
hellooooo
A Jack in a box
Jack in a box
Laa-Laa and Po
thought the Jack in a box
was very surprising
Very surprising
Oh all gone all gone
Jack in the box!
Ohhhh
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa Eh-oh Po
Look!
Oh what's that?
What's that?
It was a box
It box
Box
But this was no ordinary box
It no ordinary box
No ordinary box
What's in the box
hellooooo!
A Jack in a box
Jack in a box
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa and Po
thought the Jack in a box
was very surprising
Very surprising
hello hellooooo
Run away! Run away!
Run away!
And then the box disappeared
All gone all gone
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa Po
Boo!
Eh-oh
Boo! Boo! Boo!
Uh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
something appeared from far away
Eh-oh
Ohh what's that?
It was a watering can
Watering can
Po watered the flowers
with the watering can
Water flowers
Po water flowers
Oh!
What enormous flowers
'normous
It must have been
a magic watering can
Magic
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Po
Po watered Laa-Laa's ball
Oh Po water Laa-Laa ball
Look
What an enormous ball
Enormous ball
'normous
Thank you Po
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye Po
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Po
Po watered Tinky Winky's bag
Po water bag
Look!
What an enormous bag
Enormous
'normous
Thank you Po
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye Po
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Po
Po watered Dipsy's hat
Po water Dipsy hat
Water hat?
Oh look
What an enormous hat
Enormous hat
'normous
Thank you Po
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Po
hat!
Laa-Laa loved
her ball enormously
Laa-Laa love
And Tinky Winky
loved his bag enormously
Love bag enormously
And Dipsy
loved his hat enormously
Dipsy love hat enormously
And then the watering
can disappeared
All gone all gone all gone
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa decided to go for a walk
Laa-Laa go walk
Laa-Laa hadn't gone very far
when something appeared
from far away
Oh what's that?
It was a golden tree
Golden tree
The golden tree
had silver leaves
Oh look
What a beautiful
gold and silver tree
Laa-Laa wanted Tinky Winky
Dipsy and Po
to visit the gold and silver tree
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
visit the gold and silver tree
So Laa-Laa went to fetch them
Laa-Laa fetch the Tinky Winky
and the Dipsy and the Po
Tinky Winky! Dipsy! Po!
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
see the gold and silver tree?
Pardon?
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
see the gold and silver tree?
see gold and silver tree?
Yes
Ohh
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
followed Laa-Laa
Follow Laa-Laa follow Laa-Laa
Follow Laa-Laa
Look look
Ohh
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Po
thought the gold and silver tree
was very beautiful
Very beautiful
Gold and silver tree
very beautiful
And then the gold and
silver tree disappeared
Ah no no
Oww all gone all gone
Big hug
Teletubbies
love each other very much
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye