Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One One
Two Two
Three Three
Four Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky Tinky Winky
Dipsy Dipsy
Laa-Laa Laa-Laa
Po Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Say hello
E oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Teletubbies Teletubbies
Big hug
Uh oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone
Yeeee
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
hello hello
Come and see my top shoes
My name is Laura
Would you like to see my top shoes
Top shoes...
These are my top shoes
Come on,follow me to the garden
Bye bye...
Good bye good bye
Walking dance
hooray
Well done bravo bravo
that's terribly well good well done
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
it was Po's turn to wear the skirt
Skirt skirt
Eh-oh
Po
Yeeee
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Po
Big hug
Then it was time for Tinky Winky
to wear the skirt
Tinky Winky turn
Tinky Winky turn Tinky Winky turn
here are
Tinky Winky skirt
Ahhh
Bye-bye Po
Bye-bye
Oh yeee Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Big hug
Then it was Laa-Laa's turn
to wear the skirt
Laa-Laa turn
Oh Tinky Winky
it Laa-Laa turn now
Ow
here are
That's nice thank you
Tinky Winky Thank you
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Then it was Dipsy's turn
to wear the skirt
Oh no
Oh Dipsy turn to wear the skirt
Uh-oh
here are Dipsy
Run away
Dipsy Oh it Dipsy turn
Dipsy Oh it Dipsy turn to wear the skirt
Uh-oh Run away
Dipsy Dipsy turn
Run away Run away
Dipsy Dipsy to wear the skirt
Oh no
All gone All gone
Running away dance
Eh-oh
hooray
Again again
Round and round dance
how clever that's lovely dancing
lovely bravo that's terribly good
Eh-oh
Look look
What's that What's that
Splashing dance
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Dipsy
hooray
Eh-oh
Trit trot trit trot
Falling down dance
Eh-oh
Boo Eh-oh
Tip-toe dance
Ohh
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy saw a beautiful flower
Beautiful flower
he jumped for joy
Jump for joy
Eh-oh
Ball
Laa-Laa jumped to catch the ball
jump to catch the ball
Eh-oh
Po jumped on her scooter
Po jump on the scooter
Yeee
But Tinky Winky jumped for fun
Tinky Winky jump for fun
Oh look at that look
Very graceful bravo
well done very good
After all that jumping
Tinky Winky was very tired
Very tired
Tinky Winky Dipsy
Laa-Laa Po
hello
hello,my name is lndia
We're dancing.Come and see
We're dancing
Goodbye
Jumping dance
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo
Boo he-he-he. Boo he-he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye