Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky bag
Look! hat , ha-at , ha-at
Eh-oh
Eh-oh , the ball , wee
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies were very busy
Very busy
When something appeared in the sky
Ohh
Ohhh
What' s that? What' s that?
It was a cloud
Ohh, cloud
Ohhhh
What a lot of clouds
And it began to snow
It snow
Snow
Snow, look snow
Snow, ooh, snow
Run away
Run away?
Run away!
haven't they seen snow before?
how silly, how silly
It snowed and it snowed and it snowed
Until everything in Teletubbyland
was covered in snow
It 'snowing , snow , lovely
The Teletubbies went out in the snow
Ohh , ohh , out in the snow
out in the snow
Uh-oh
Again again
Big hug
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland everything
was covered in snow
Eh-oh
The house was covered in snow
house covered in snow
The trees were covered in snow
Trees covered in snow
Everything in Teletubbyland
was covered in snow
Everything covered in snow
So the Teletubbies went to see
See, see, see
The Teletubbies hadn't gone very far
when Tinky Winky saw something
covered in snow
Ohh , look
Ohh , What' s that? What' s that?
Tinky Winky thought he had seen
something like it before
It was Tinky Winky's bag
Tinky Winky bag
Then Dipsy saw something
covered in snow
Ohh, look
What' s that?
Ohh, What' s that?
Dipsy thought he had seen
something like it before
It was Dipsy' s hat
Dipsy hat
Ohh, Dipsy hat
Then Laa-Laa saw something
covered in snow
Look
What' s that?
Laa-Laa thought she had seen
something like it before
It was Laa-Laa' s ball
Laa-Laa ball
Then Po saw something covered in snow
Look
What' s that?
Po thought she had seen
something like it before
It was Po' s scooter
Scooter
Po scooter
Ahh, scooter
The Teletubbies were very happy
Very happy
She' s going much to fast, too fast
and in the snow too, much too fast
Be careful Po
Snow is very slippery
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky, Dipsy and Laa-Laa
saw something covered in snow
Look!
What' s that?
Tinky Winky
Dipsy and Laa-Laa thought they
had seen something like it before
Eh-oh
It was Po covered in snow
Po
Tinky Winky
Dipsy and Laa-Laa love Po
Love Po
Big hug
And Teletubbies love
each other very much
One day in Teletubbyland
everything was covered in snow
Uh-oh!
All the Teletubbies were walking
very carefully in the snow
because snow can be very slippery
Very slippery, very slippery
Po was walking carefully
Po walk carefully
Laa-Laa was walking carefully
Laa-Laa walking carefully
Dipsy was walking
carefully in the snow
Dipsy walking carefully
But Tinky Winky wasn't walking
very carefully at all
Not carefully, not at all
Uh-oh!
Be careful Tinky Winky
Snow can be very slippery
Careful Tinky Winky
snow can be very slippery
Tinky Winky slipped
Tinky Winky began to slide
Uh-oh!
Oh dear, oh dear
Again again
Tinky Winky liked sliding
Like sliding, yee! sliding! sliding
Sliding! sliding
Laa-Laa and Po wanted to play sliding
Play sliding! sliding! sliding
Sliding
Uh-oh!
Again, again
Tinky Winky, Laa-Laa
and Po liked playing sliding
Like sliding, like sliding
Sliding! Sliding
Uh-oh!
Sliding! sliding
Tinky Winky, Laa-Laa and Po
wanted Dipsy to play sliding
Dipsy! Dipsy! Sliding
Uh-oh!
Uh-oh! Oh-no! Uh-oh!
Dipsy! Dipsy! Sliding
But Dipsy didn' t want to play sliding
Ohh! Dipsy! sliding! sliding! sliding
Uh-oh! oh-no
What clever sliding
Clever sliding
Tinky Winky, Laa-Laa and Po love Dipsy
Big hug
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
the Teletubbies were
very busy in the snow
Very busy
Tinky Winky and Dipsy
were making footprints
Foot prints
Po was making Po prints
Po laughs
Po prints
And Laa-Laa made a snowball
Laa-Laa snowball
Snowball
Laa-Laa showed her snowball
to Tinky Winky, Dipsy and Po
Laa-Laa showed snowball to
Tinky Winky, Dipsy and Po
Eh-oh, Laa-Laa
Look! snowball
Ohh! snowball
Tinky Winky , Dipsy and Po thought
Laa-Laa' s snowball was very small
Very small?
But Laa-Laa loved her small snowball
Laa-Laa love the small snowball
Then Laa-Laa' s small
snowball began to roll
It roll
And as Laa-Laa' s snowball
rolled it grew
Bigger, and bigger
And bigger
Bigger and bigger and bigger
What a big snowball
Snowball
Snowball! Snowball!
Uh-oh!
What a big snowball
What a snowy mess
The Noo-noo tidied up
Noo-noo tidy up, Noo-noo tidy up
Clever Noo-noo
Big hug Noo-noo
The Teletubbies love the Noo-noo
Love the Noo-noo
And the Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh- oh
One day in Teletubbyland all
the Teletubbies were making snowballs
Snowballs, making snowballs
Tinky Winky was making a snowball
Snowball
Dipsy was making a snowball
Laa-Laa was making a snowball
Snowball
And Po was making a snowball
Tinky Winky had made a small snowball
Small snowball
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Dipsy' s snowball was bigger
than Tinky Winky' s snowball
Dipsy' s snowball bigger
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Tinky Winky, Eh-oh Dipsy
Laa-Laa' s snowball was bigger than
Tinky Winky' s snowball
but smaller than Dipsy' s snowball
Laa-Laa snow ball bigger than
the Tinky Winky
smaller than the Dipsy snowball
Ohhh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky, Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
And Po' s snowball was the
biggest snowball of all
Biggest
Biggest!
What lovely snowballs
Lovely snowballs
The Teletubbies decided to use their
snowballs to build a snow Tubby
Snow Tubby, snow Tubby
Po' s snowball was just the right
size for a snow Tubby body
Snow Tubby, Snow Tubby
And Dipsy' s snowball was just
the right size for a snow Tubby' s head
Uh-oh!
So Dipsy put his snowball
on top of Po' s snowball
Snow Tubby, Snow Tubby
Yee
Tinky Winky and Laa-Laa' s snowballs
were just the right size
for snow Tubby arms
Snow Tubby, Snow Tubby
The snow Tubby was finished
Snow Tubby finished
Snow Tubby, Snow Tubby
Tinky Winky loved the snow Tubby so much
that he gave it his bag to hold
Tinky Winky bag
here are
Snow Tubby bag
Dipsy loved the snow Tubby so much
that he gave it his hat to wear
Dipsy hat
here are
Snow Tubby hat, snow Tubby hat
Laa-Laa loved the snow Tubby so much
that she gave it her ball to play with
Laa-Laa ball
here are
Snow Tubby ball
Po loved the snow Tubby so much
that she gave it her scooter to ride
Scooter
here are
Snow Tubby scooter
What a happy snow Tubby
happy snow Tubby, yes
Big hug
Teletubbies love each other very much
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh-oh oh-no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo! he, he, he. Boo he, he, he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye