Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
Naughty Noo-noo
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
What a lot of Tubby Toast
What a lot
Laa-Laa wanted
a piece of Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Laa-Laa couldn't reach
Uh-oh!
Dipsy wanted
a pierce of Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
But he couldn't reach
Dipsy can't reach
Tinky Winky wanted
a piece of Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
But he couldn't reach
Tinky Winky can't reach
Uh-oh!
Po wanted a piece of Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
So she took the nearest one
Now everybody can
reach the Tubby Toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Sponges
Tubby Sponges!
Please may we have
the Tubby Sponges?
Tubby Sponges!
Number one hands
hands
Wash wash wash
Tubby Tubby Tubby
Number two elbows
Elbows
Wash wash wash
Tubby Tubby Tubby
Number three knees
Knees
Knees!
Wash wash wash
Tubby Tubby Tubby
Number four feet
Feet
Feet!
Wash wash wash
Tubby Tubby Tubby
Number five tummies
Tummies
Uh-oh!
Now all the Teletubbies
are all clean
All clean
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies
had special things to do
Special things to do
Eh-oh
Tinky Winky was going to
jump all the way along the path
Tinky Winky jump along the path look
Ohh
Uh-oh!
Oh
Never mind Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
Dipsy was going to walk all the way
around the house without stopping
Dipsy walk around the house
hooray Dipsy
Pardon?
Owww
Oh dear Dipsy stopped
Never mind Dipsy
Eh-oh
Laa-Laa was going to throw her ball
up as high as the clouds
Ohh Laa-Laa throw the ball
up high high clouds look
One two three hooray
Uh-oh! Oh dear
Never mind Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Po was going to ride her scoter
all the way up
to the top of the steep steep hill
Po scooter hill look
Oh dear
Owww
Never mind Po
Tinky Winky tried again
Tinky Winky try again again
Again again
Tinky Winky tried again to
jump all the way along the path
Tinky Winky try again
jump along path look
Oh
hooray
Tinky Winky did it
Tinky Winky did it!
Big hug
Dipsy tries again
one more time
Eh-oh Dipsy try again
Again again
Dipsy tried again to walk all the way
around the house without stopping
Dipsy walk all the way round house
Ohh
Yes
Dipsy did it
Dipsy did it!
Big hug! Big hug! Big hug!
Big hug
Laa-Laa tried again one more time
Laa-Laa tried again again
Again again
Laa-Laa tried again to throw
the ball up as high as the clouds
Laa-Laa try again throw
the ball up high in the clouds
Ohh
One two three hooray
Wooooo hooray
Laa-Laa did it
Big hug
Po tried again one last time
Again again again
Again again
Po tried again to ride her scooter
up the steep steep hill
Po scooter up hill look!
Ohh
Yeeeee
hooray
Po did it
What clever Teletubbies
Clever Teletubbies
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Custard
hooray Tubby custard!
Tubby custard!
Tubby custard! Tubby custard!
hooray
Uh-oh!
The Tubby Custard machine
wouldn't stop
Wouldn't stop
More and more Tubby Custard
Too much Tubby Custard
Uh-oh!
Much too much Tubby Custard
Po wanted the Tubby
Custard Machine to stop
Stop
So Po turned the Tubby
Custard machine off
Tubby custard off
Ohh
Look! Look
What a lot of Tubby Custard
Lot of Tubby Custard
Uh-oh!
It was time for
the Noo-noo to tidy up
Noo-noo tidy up Noo-noo
Ohhhhh
Ohh
Noo-noo tidy up
Clever Noo-noo
The Teletubbies love the Noo-noo
very much
Love the Noo-noo
Big hug
Tinky Winky
Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
the Teletubbies were very busy
Tinky Winky loves his bag
and Po loves her scooter
Tinky Winky bag
Po scooter
Dipsy loves his hat
and Laa-Laa loves her ball
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa ball
Then it was time for
the Teletubbies to go to bed
Owww go to bed oww
Go to bed
Tinky Winky took his bag
with him to bed
Tinky Winky bag bed
Po took her scooter to bed
Po scooter bed
Dipsy took his hat
with him to bed
And Laa-Laa took her ball to bed
Laa-Laa ball bed
Ohh
Oh no
Uh-oh!
Oh biddly cheese!
Laa-Laa ball bed
Laa-Laa ball?
Laa-Laa ball
Laa-Laa loves her ball
And Teletubbies
love each other very much
Big hug
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye