E-oh
Teletubbies everywhere
E-oh E-oh E-oh
One Po Two Pos
Oh oh
Two Pos One Po
Bye bye Bye bye
Near and far
E-oh
hello Dipsy
hello La La
Near
Ooh Near
Near Near Near Near
Dipsy
E-oh
hello Dipsy
hello La La
Dipsy
Far
It's far
Dipsy is far Yes yes
hey hey Dipsy
hello La La
hello Dipsy
Near
Near near
Big hug
Big hug hug
Bye bye
E-oh Tinky Winky Oooh Oooh
Oh oh E-oh
E-oh
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big big hug hug Big hug
Bye bye
Bye bye Bye bye
E-oh
Teletubbies everywhere
E-oh E-oh E-oh E-oh E-oh
E-oh
Brown
Ooh look
Brown Brown Brown brown
brown brown brown Brown
Brown
E-oh Oh
E-oh E-oh
Behind the tree
Eee Behind the tree
La La hind the tree Oh oh
Behind
E-oh E-oh
ln front of the tree
Front of the tree La La in front of tree
Behind the tree
Behind again La La hind the tree
ln front of the tree
La La in front of tree
La La hind the tree
All gone all gone
Bye bye
Oh oh Dipsy Eee
Oh oh look E-oh E-oh
E-oh
Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
Bye bye
Bye bye Bye bye bye bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Teletubbies
Say hello
hello
Tinky Winky Dipsy La La Po
Teletubbies
Teletubbies Big hug
E-oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
it was a day for dancing
Dipsy danced out of bed
E-oh Dipsy dance
Dipsy dance
E-oh
La La danced while
she made Tubby custard
Oh Tubby custard Tubby custard
La La dance
Weeee La La Eeee La la la
La la la la la la la
hey hey
La La dance with Tubby custard
E-oh
Tinky Winky danced with Po
Oh Tinky Winky dance with Po
E-oh Tinky Winky dance Po
Tinky Winky dance with Po
Ah ahh
Bye bye
What a happy dancing day
happy dancing day
Teletubbies love to dance
And Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug Ahhh
E-oh
what's that
What's that?
what's that?
E-oh Dipsy
E-oh La La
Ooh ooh What's that
E-oh
What's that?
E-oh Dipsy E-oh La La
E-oh Tinkle Winkle
What's that?
What's that
E-oh
Oh what's that?
E-oh Tinky Winky E-oh Dipsy
E-oh La La
E-oh Po
What's that?
Gone now
All gone All gone
E-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
La La
Po
Oh oh look
hello hello hello hello hello hello
hello my name's Radhika
My name's Benico
My name's Anuska
My name's Annabel
My name's Anthony
Come and play
Vinatta's going to tell us a story
Never-ending story
hello hello
My name is Venatta
I'm going to tell you a story called the fox
Long long ago in the lovely thick forest
there lived a clever fox
he was a clever fox
Clever fox loved to eat
Every morning he went out into the forest
And he ate and he ate and he ate
Mmmm he said I'm full
now I can go and play
And so off he went to play in the forest
When it got dark clever fox
went home again
And went to sleep
One day clever fox went into the forest
he looked and looked and looked
but he couldn't find anything to eat
Oh no he said I'm so hungry
I want something to eat
What shall I do?
Now I must think he said
And he thought and he thought
and he thought
Oh suddenly he heard a noise
Whirr whoosh whirr whoosh
whirr whoosh
Ah said clever fox what's that?
I'm scared and he hid behind a tree
Oh but my tummy is rumbling he said
I mustn't be scared said clever fox
go and see what the noise is
So he went carefully
And slowly
And when he got to where the noise
was he peeped out
and what do you think he saw?
There was a big drum and
a branch of a tree was rubbing against it
whirrr whoosh whirrr whoossh
And beside the drum was
lots and lots and lots of food
hurray said clever fox
I'm so glad I was brave
I can eat all this food now
And so he ate and ate and ate
Mmm lots of food yes
And went off to play into the forest
Bye bye
E-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbis had their favourite things
Tinky Winky had the ball
Tinky Winky Ball Oh oh
Dipsy had the scooter
Dipsy Scooter Oh oh
La La had the bag
La La Bag Oh oh
And Po had the hat
Po hat Oh oh
Oh oh
But Tinky Winky wanted the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Oh oh Oh oh Oh oh
Dipsy wanted the hat
Dipsy hat Oh oh
La La wanted the ball
La La Ball
Oh oh
La La ball
And Po wanted the scooter
Po Scooter
Oh oh
So the Teletubbies swapped
their favourite things around
Swap Swap round Swap Swap swap
Tinky Winky gave Dipsy the ball
And Dipsy gave Tinky Winky the scooter
here are Dipsy
here are Tinky Winky
Thank you Dipsy
Thank you Tinky Winky Thank you
Dipsy gave La La the ball
And La La gave Dipsy the bag
here are La La
here are Dipsy Oh oh
Thank you La La
Thank you Dipsy thank you thank you
See La La ball
Dipsy bag
La La ball
Dipsy gave Tinky Winky the bag
And Tinky Winky gave Dipsy the scooter
here are Dipsy
here are Tinky Winky
Thank you Tinky Winky
Thank you Dipsy Tinky Winky bag
Twinky Winky bag Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy gave La La the scooter
And La La gave Dipsy the ball
here are La La
here are Dipsy
Thank you La La
Thank you Dipsy
La La gave Po the scooter
here are Po
Thank you La La
Ride it ride it ride it
La La took back her ball
Dipsy Dipsy
here are La La
Oh thank you Dipsy thank you thank you
And Po passed the hat to Dipsy
Oh oh hat hat here are Dipsy
Thank you Po
hat Dipsy's hat Dipsy's hat
hat Thank you Po
Dipsy's hat Dipsy's hat
All the Teletubbies were very happy
to have their favourite things back
Very happy very happy very happy
happy very happy very happy
Tinky Winky bag Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy hat Dipsy hat
Dipsy hat hat hat hat hat hat hat
La La ball
Teletubbies love their favourite things
Favourite things
And the Teletubbies love
each other very much
Big hug Big hug Ahh Big hug Ahh
Time for Tubby bye bye
Nooo
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye La La
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
Nooo
Bye bye Tinky Winky
Bye bye
Bye bye Dipsy
Bye bye La La
Bye bye
Bye bye Po
The sun was setting in the sky
Teletubbies say bye bye
Bye bye