Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa
and Po his from Dipsy
Dipsy closed his eyes
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa
and Po went to hide
hide hide hide
Laa-Laa hide
Laa-Laa hid between the beds
Laa-Laa hide between beds
hide sshhh
Po hide
Po hid under the arch
Po under arch
Po hide
Tinky Winky hid behind the Tubby Toaster
Tinky Winky hide
Dipsy was ready to look for
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po
Uh-oh!
First Dipsy looked for Laa-Laa
Dipsy look Laa-Laa
Shhhh
But Dipsy couldn't find Laa-Laa
Dipsy can't find Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Next Dipsy looked for Po
Dipsy look for Po
Shhhh
But Dipsy couldn't find Po
Dipsy can't find Po
Dipsy couldn't find Po
Eh-oh
Shhh
Dipsy looked for Tinky Winky
Uh-oh!
Shhhh
But Dipsy couldn't find Tinky Winky
Dipsy can't find Tinky Winky
Dipsy couldn't find
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa or Po
Can't find Tinky Winky Laa-Laa or Po
But then it was time for
the Noo-Noo to tidy up
Eh-oh
The Noo-Noo tidies up between the beds
The Noo-Noo found Laa-Laa
Noo-Noo found Laa-Laa Noo-Noo!
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Dipsy
Dipsy found Laa-Laa
The Noo-Noo tides up under the arch
Uh-oh!
The Noo-Noo found Po
Owww Noo-Noo find Po
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Dipsy
Dipsy found Po
Eh-oh
The Noo-Noo tidied up
behind the Tubby Toaster
Uh-oh!
The Noo-Noo found Tinky Winky
Noo-Noo found Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy
Dipsy found Tinky Winky
Big hug
Dipsy found all the Teletubbies
Clever Dipsy
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
Tubby Toast! Tubby Toast!
Dipsy yes
Tinky Winky toast
Po toast
Oh no
Where the toast gone?
Where the toast gone
Look!
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland something
appeared from far away
Eh-oh
What's that?
It was a wall
Oh wall
Po heard Laa-Laa coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Po
What's that?
Pardon
Wall
What's that?
Wall?
Wall
Again again
Oh where Po?
Po was behind the wall
Eh-oh
Po behind the wall
Oh where gone
Po was in front of the wall
Po in front of wall
Po front of wall
Where Po?
Po was behind the wall
Eh-oh
Po behind the wall
Po?
Where Laa-Laa?
Po was in front of the wall
and Laa-Laa was behind the wall
Laa-Laa!
Po!
Po?
Laa-Laa?
Uh-oh!
Eh-oh
Po?
Laa-Laa
Po!
Laa-Laa!
Laa-Laa and Po
heard Tinky Winky coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Laa-Laa Eh-oh Po
What's that?
Wall
Pardon
Po and Laa-Laa showed
Tinky Winky the wall
What's that?
Wall
Wall?
Po and Laa-Laa showed Tinky Winky
a game with the wall
Show Tinky Winky
Look!
Po and Laa-Laa walked around the wall
Round the wall
Po and Laa-Laa walked
around the wall the other way
Other way
Po and Laa-Laa stood behind the wall
Behind the wall
Po and Laa-Laa stood in front of the wall
ln front of the wall
Then it was Tinky Winky's turn to play
a game with the wall
Tinky Winky turn
Tinky Winky walked around the wall
Around the wall
Tinky Winky walked
around the wall the other way
The other way
Tinky Winky stood behind the wall
Behind the wall
Tinky Winky looked over the wall
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po
heard Dipsy coming
Dipsy coming
So Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po
hid behind the wall
hide behind wall
Eh-oh
Dipsy saw the wall
Oh what's that?
What's that?
It was a wall
Wall
But Dipsy didn't see Tinky Winky
Laa-Laa and Po behind the wall
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po?
hooray!
Where Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po?
And then the wall disappeared
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa and Po
Dipsy
Big hug
Eh-oh
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
wondered where Po was
Where Po? Where Po? Where Po?
So Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
went to look for Po
Tinky Winky Dipsy
and Laa-Laa look for Po
Po! Po!
Tinky Winky went
looking for Po in the house
Tinky Winky look Po in the house
Dipsy went looking for Po
among the flowers
Dipsy look Po flowers
Where Po?
Where Po
Eh-oh
And Laa-Laa went looking for Po
far far over the hills
Laa-Laa look for Po
Po! Po!
Tinky Winky couldn't find Po in the house
Can't find Po
Dipsy couldn't find Po among the flowers
Po! Po!
But far far over the hills Laa-Laa found Po
Ohhh! Look
Po was lying fast asleep under a big tree
Look! Po fast asleep under tree
Shh asleep ahhh
So Laa-Laa went to tell
Tinky Winky and Dipsy
Laa-Laa tell Tinky Winky and Dipsy
Shhh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa told Tinky Winky and Dipsy
the story of Po
Laa-Laa tell Tinky Winky
and Dipsy story Po
Laa-Laa Tinky Winky Dipsy story Po
Laa-Laa told Tinky Winky and Dipsy
that far far over the hills
there was a big tree and under the tree
Po was lying fast asleep
Far far away over the hills a big tree
And and under the tree
Po lying fast asleep
Ohhh
Far far away over the hills a big tree
Under the tree Po lying fast asleep
Yes!
So Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
went to see Po
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa see Po
See Po
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa see Po
Look!
Ohhh Look!
Po asleep shhh
Eh-oh
Po!
Eh-oh Tinky
Winky Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Po
Big hug Big hug
Big hug
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa love Po
And Teletubbies love each other very much
Big hug
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye