Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Po was looking at the sky
Po look at sky
Blue blue blue sky blue
Blue blue blue
Look
White white white clouds white
White white white
White white white white
White white white clouds white
White white white
Look!
Grey grey grey clouds grey
Grey grey grey
Grey grey grey grey
Grey grey grey clouds grey
Grey grey grey
Uh-oh! Look!
Rain rain rain rain
Rain rain rain
Run away! Run away!
Rain rain run away
Urghhh
Look!
Blue blue blue puddle blue
Blue blue blue
Look!
Po!
Po Po Po puddle Po
Po Po Po
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland the wind blew
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies were very busy
Very busy
Tinky Winky was marching with the bag
Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy was dancing in his hat
Dipsy hat
ha-at ha-at ha-at
Laa-Laa was playing with her ball
Laa-Laa ball
And Po was riding her scooter
Po 'cooter
What busy Teletubbies
Busy Teletubbies
One day in Teletubbyland
all the Teletubbies were very busy
when a big wind blew
Uh-oh!
Big wind
The wind blew on Dipsy's hat
Uh-oh!
Dipsy's hat
The wind blew on Laa-Laa's ball
Uh-oh!
Oh no
Oh no Laa-Laa ball
The wind blew on Tinky Winky's bag
Uh-oh!
Oh no
Oh dear Tinky Winky bag
And the wind blew on Po's scooter
Uh-oh!
Oh no
Oh dear scooter Uh-oh!
Oh dear
All the Teletubbies' favourite things
had blown away
Oh dear
favourite things blow away
Owww
The Teletubbies wanted to
have their favourite things back
Back back back back
favourite things back
So the Teletubbies sang
a come back everything song
Come back everything
Come back
And then the wind began to drop
Tinky Winky's bag came back
Yee! Tinky Winky bag
Ahh Tinky Winky bag
Dipsy's hat came back
Dipsy hat
Laa-Laa's ball came back
Ball! Laa-Laa ball
hooray Laa-Laa ball
And Po's scooter came back
'cooter!
'cooter 'cooter
And the Teletubbies were very happy
Very happy
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
something fell out of the sky
lt landed on Tinky Winky's head
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky wondered what it was
What's that?
lt was a cloud
Cloud
lt was Tinky Winky's special cloud
Tinky Winky's special cloud
Tinky Winky went to show
his special cloud to the other Teletubbies
Special cloud
Eh-oh
Ohhh Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa wondered
what Tinky Winky had on his head
What on head?
Pardon
What's on head?
Tinky Winky special cloud
Ohhh Tinky Winky special cloud
Oww
Laa-Laa thought Tinky Winky's
special cloud was beautiful
Beautiful
So Tinky Winky went to show Po
Show Po
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Po wondered
what Tinky Winky had on his head
What Tinky Wink head?
Tinky Winky
Yes
what head
Pardon
What head?
Tinky Winky special cloud
Pardon
Po thought Tinky Winky's
special cloud was beautiful
Beautiful
So Tinky Winky went to show Dipsy
Show Dipsy
Bye-bye Po
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Dipsy wondered
what Tinky Winky had on his head
What's that?
Pardon
Tinky Winky's special cloud
Tinky Winky special cloud
Ohhhhh
Bye-bye cloud
Tinky Winky was sad now
that the cloud had gone
Tinky Winky sad cloud
Tinky Winky has nothing on his head
Nothing head
Tinky Winky nothing head
So Dipsy gave Tinky Winky his hat
to wear to cheer him up
Dipsy hat
here are Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa remembered the snow
Oh the snow snow snow snow
Oh the snow snow
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Dipsy was out for a walk
when he heard something very unusual
What's that?
Dipsy looked at it
but he had never seen anything
like it before
What's that?
lt was a book
Book
And on the front of the book
was a picture of Dipsy wearing his hat
Dipsy wearing hat
Open the book Dipsy
On the first page
was a big picture of Teletubbyland
Teletubbyland
Dipsy turned the page
Turn the page
On the next page was
a picture of Teletubbyland with a big cloud
A big cloud
Dipsy turned the page
Turn the page
On the next page
was a picture of Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh
Dipsy turned the next page
of the magic book
On the next page was a picture
of the cloud raining on Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky cloud and rain
Pardon
Oh no
Uh-oh!
Dipsy turned the next page
Turn the next page
On the next page was a picture of
Tinky Winky holding an umbrella
Tinky Winky umbrella
hooray!
Dipsy turned the next page
Turn the next page
On the next page
the sun was shining brightly
Sun shinning brightly
All gone
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
One day in Teletubbyland
it was raining
Eh-oh
The Teletubbies had to stay indoors
stay indoors
lt rained and it rained and it rained
And then lt stopped
Eh-oh
And then Dipsy looked out of the window
and saw something special
Dipsy window
Special
Dipsy called Tinky Winky Laa-Laa
and Po to come and see
Dipsy call
Tinky Winky! Laa-Laa! Po!
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Laa-Laa Eh-oh Po
Look!
Owww what's that?
What's that?
lt was something very special
Something very special
lt was a rainbow
Rainbow
The Teletubbies went to see the rainbow
Rainbow rainbow see rainbow
But the rainbow was very far away
Very far away
Red orange yellow green
blue indigo violet
What a beautiful rainbow
Beautiful rainbow
And then the rainbow disappeared
Ohhh
All gone all gone
Big hug
Teletubbies love each other very much
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he
No No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye