Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Boo! Eh-oh
The grand old Duke of York
he had ten thousand men
he marched them up
to the top of the hill
Oh the top of the hill
And he marched them down again
Oww down again
And when they were up they were up
Oh no not again
And when they were
down they were down
And when they were only halfway up
They were neither up not down
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Laa-Laa was eating her Tubby Toast
Laa-Laa eat Tubby Toast
When she heard a noise
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Again again again
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Again again again
Laa-Laa liked the song do much
that she made up a special dance
Special dance
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Run away! Run away!
Laa-Laa heard somebody coming
Somebody coming
Weeeeee
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Big hug
Dipsy wondered what Laa-Laa was doing
What Laa-Laa doing
So Laa-Laa showed Dipsy
her special dance
Special dance look
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Run away! Run away!
Laa-Laa and Dipsy heard
somebody coming
Somebody coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Tinky Winky wondered what
Laa-Laa and Dipsy were doing
What doing Laa-Laa Dipsy?
So Laa-Laa and Dipsy showed
Tinky Winky their special dance
Special dance look
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Run away! Run away!
Big hug
Laa-Laa Dipsy and Tinky Winky
heard somebody coming
Somebody coming
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Po wondered what Laa-Laa
Dipsy and Tinky Winky were doing
What doing
So Laa-Laa Dipsy and Tinky Winky
showed Po their special dance
Special dance look
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Run away! Run away!
Big hug
Po wanted to dance too
Po dance too
So the Teletubbies danced
their special dance again
Dance again
hey diddle diddle
The cat and the fiddle
The cow jumped over the moon
The little dog laughed to see such fun
And the dish ran away with the spoon
Run away! Run away!
Big hug
Again again
Uh-oh!
Shh somebody's coming
somebody's coming
Eh-oh
Jack and Jill went up the hill
to fetch a pail of water
Jack fell down all the way down
And Jill came tumbling after
Ohhh
Again again again
Jack and Jill went up the hill
to fetch a pail of water
Jack and Jill up hill
fetch pail of water
Jack fell down all the down
Jack fell down all the way down
And Jill came tumbling after
Jill came tumbling after
Very good bravo well done very good
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Po was eating her Tubby Toast
when she heard a noise
Ohh
Twinkle twinkle little star
how I wonder what you are
Up above the world so high
Like a diamond in the sky
Twinkle twinkle little star
how I wonder what you are
Again again
Twinkle twinkle little star
how I wonder what you are
Up above the world so high
Like a diamond in the sky
Twinkle twinkle little star
how I wonder what you are
Yee!
Owww
But then Po heard another noise
Ohh what's that
It's magical music
Magical music
Po wondered where the magical music
was coming from
Where come from
The magical music was not coming
from under the table
Not under table
The magical music was not
coming from out of the window
Not out window
The magical music was not
coming from the controls
Not from controls
But then Po looked up
Ahhh
What's that? What's that?
It was a star a magical star indoors
Star star
Ahh
Again again
Ohh
Star ahhh
Po heard Tinky Winky Dipsy
and Laa-Laa coming back
Tinky Winky Dipsy and Laa-Laa
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa Eh-oh Dipsy
Eh-oh Tinky Winky
Eh-oh Po
Po wanted to show Tinky Winky
Dipsy and Laa-Laa the magical star
Look!
Ohh
What's that?
Star
Owwwww
All gone
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Eh-oh
Pat a cake pat a cake
Baker's man
Bake me a cake as fast as you can
Pat it and prick it and mark it with B
And put it in the oven for baby and me
Again again
Pat a cake pat a cake
Baker's man
Bake me a cake as fast as you can
Pat it and prick it and mark it with B
And put it in the oven for baby and me
Pat a cake pat a cake
Baker's man
Bake me a cake as fast as you can
Pat it and prick it and mark it with B
And put it in the oven for baby and me
Owww
Weeee
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Pat a cake
Pardon
Pat a cake?
Pat a cake!
Oww pat a cake
Again again again!
Pat a cake pat a cake
Baker's man
Bake me a cake as fast as you can
Pat it and prick it and mark it with B
And put it in the oven for baby and me
Again
Again again
Pat a cake pat a cake
Baker's man
Bake me a cake as fast as you can
Pat it and prick it and mark it with B
And put it in the oven for baby and me
hello hello hello hello
One day in Teletubbyland something
appeared from far away
Oh look a spider a spider!
It's only a toy
Look at that!
It's disappeared
Eh-oh
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Little Miss Laa-Laa tubbety tubbet
Eating Tubby custard
That what Laa-Laa do yes
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Little Miss Laa-Laa tubbety tubbet
Eating Tubby custard
Along came a spider
Along came a spider?
And sat down beside her
And frightened Miss Muffet away
Uh-oh!
Run away! Run away!
It's only a toy one it's only a toy
Look at that it's disappeared
Eh-oh
Tubby custard! Tubby custard!
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Tinky Winky and Dipsy sat on a tubbet
Eating Tubby custard
Uh-oh!
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Dipsy and Tinky Winky sat down
on tubbet eating Tubby custard
Tubby custard
Along came a spider
Along came a spider?
And sat down beside her
And sat down beside Tinky Winky
and Dipsy
Uh-oh!
And frightened Miss Muffet away
Run away! Run away!
It's only a toy it's only a toy one
Look at that it's disappeared
Eh-oh
Tubby Custard
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Little Miss Po sat on tubbet
Eating Tubby custard
That what Po do
Little Miss Muffet sat on a tuffet
Eating her curds and whey
Little Miss Po sat on tubbet
Eating Tubby custard
Along came a spider
Along came a spider?
And sat down beside her
Uh-oh! Look
And frightened Miss Muffet away
Ohh
Po frighten spider away! Shhh
Bye-bye spider
Eh-oh
humpty Dumpty sat on wall
humpty Dumpty had a great fall
All the Kings horses
and all the King's men
Couldn't put humpty together again
Ohhhh
Pardon
Again again
humpty Dumpty sat on wall
Ohh
humpty Dumpty had a great fall
Ohhh
All the Kings horses
and all the King's men
Couldn't put humpty together again
Oh no
Ride a cockhorse to Banbury Cross
To see a fine lady
upon a white horse
With rungs on her fingers
and bells on her toes
She shall have music
wherever she goes
Oww
Again again
Ride a cockhorse to Banbury Cross
To see a fine lady upon a white horse
With rungs on her fingers
and bells on her toes
She shall have music wherever she goes
Yeee again again
Ride a cockhorse to Banbury Cross
To see a fine lady upon a white horse
With rungs on her fingers
and bells on her toes
She shall have music wherever she goes
Big hug
Again again
Ride a cockhorse to Banbury Cross
To see a fine lady upon a white horse
With rungs on her fingers
and bells on her toes
She shall have music
wherever she goes
Big hug
Again again
Ride a cockhorse to Banbury Cross
To see a fine lady upon a white horse
With rungs on her fingers
and bells on her toes
She shall have music wherever she goes
Eh-oh
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky Dipsy Laa-Laa Po
Again again
hickory Dickory Dock
The mouse ran up the clock
The clock struck one
The mouse ran down
hickory Dickory Dock
Again again
The mouse ran up the clock
The clock struck one
One
The mouse ran down
hickory Dickory Dock
Again again
The mouse ran up the clock
The clock struck two
Uh-oh! Two
One
Two
The mouse ran down
One
Two
hickory Dickory Dock
Again again
The mouse ran up the clock
The clock struck three
Uh-oh! Three!
One two three
The mouse ran down
One
Two
Three
hickory Dickory Dock
Again again
The mouse ran up the clock
The clock struck eight
Uh-oh! Eight!
One two three four five
six seven eight
The mouse ran down
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
hickory Dickory Dock
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
No no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye