Over the hills and far away...
Teletubbies come to play
One...
One!
two...
Two!
three
Three!
four!
Four-r-r-r!
Four!
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky!
Dipsy
Dipsy!
Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa!
Po
Po!
Teletubbies
Teletubbies!
Say hello!
hello!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Teletubbies
Teletubbies!
Big hug
Uh-ohhhh
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Lah-lah-lah
Lah-lee-lah-lee-lah
Lah-lah-lah-lah-lah
Lah...
Eh-ohhh
Oh! Ohhh! Where ball?
Erm - where ball?
Oh-h-h!
Oh! Oo-ay!
Gain! Laa-Laa's ball!
Oo-ay! Wee!
Uh-ohhh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy!
Laa-Laa!
Po
hello My name's Elicia
Come and see my Nanny's garden
Come on
come and see my nanny's garden
We're going to visit nanny Bev
Oh hello Kiss kiss l'm nanny Bev
Come on in come on in
We are going in the garden
We are going to pick some of the . . .
You want to come too
cone on then come on
We went to help her in the garden
Which youwant to go and
see first the apples or the tomatoes
We carried the box
that nanny brought us into garden
all the boxes were empty
We picked the apples first
Get them in
there's frost you know
They were falling on the ground
We put the apples in the box
The apples were growing on the tree
We got loads of apples
We picked all of them off
We got green ones yellow ones
orange ones
So we're going to
pick some tomatoes now
Tomatoes in here everyone
We picked the tomatoes next
green ones and red ones
Come lets get the beans in
Next we picked the beans
You open one of these
you'll find some red ones
Elisha look here
They were green on the outside
But inside they were red
Let me help you let me help you
Let me help There
The green beans had red beans inside
When you get them in the shop they're dry
Fresh thyme smell it. . . . . .grown
Nanny Bev has got a great big garden
full of vegetables
she picks them and cooks them
and makes us dinner
Come and see what l found
l found a pumpkin
This is a pumpkin
This is a small pumpkin
Then l picked some big pumpkins
The pumkins were very big
And l'm going to put them in this box
And l was going to drop them in it
. . . put them in carefully
Big big pumpkin and
it's a dirty one and
it's a green one and
l'm going to put it right in there
that box there where the m. . .are
Just wipe all the dirt off
Come on lets put it in
They were hard to carry
l put them very carefully
in the pumpkin box
Two of us had to carry the apple box
it was so heavy
It was so heavy cos
it was full of apples
When the boxes were full
we carried everything on to the patio
l sorted everything out
l sorted it all out
Red beans
Green tomatoes
red apples and green apples
green tomatoes and red tomatoes
Green pumpkins
Coriander
Nice thyme
We ate some of the red tomatoes
The tomatoes tasted lovely
l love working in nanny's garden
Bye
Bye bye
Bye-bye! - Ohhhwww
Again! Again again!
Again! Agai - i - in!
hello my name is Elisha
come and see my nanny's garden
We're going to visit nanny Bev
Oh hello Kiss kiss l'm nanny Bev
Come on in come on in
We are going in the garden
We are going to pick some of the . . .
You want to come too
cone on then come on
We went to help her in the garden
Which youwant to go and
see first the apples or the tomatoes
We carried the box
that nanny brought us into garden
all the boxes were empty
We picked the apples first
Get them in
there's frost you know
They were falling on the ground
We put the apples in the box
The apples were growing on the tree
We got loads of apples
We picked all of them off
We got green ones yellow ones
orange ones
So we're going to
pick some tomatoes now
Tomatoes in here everyone
We picked the tomatoes next
green ones and red ones
Come lets get the beans in
Next we picked the beans
You open one of these
you'll find some red ones
Elisha look here
They were green on the outside
But inside they were red
Let me help you let me help you
Let me help There
The green beans had red beans inside
When you get them in the shop they're dry
Fresh thyme smell it. . . . . .grown
Nanny Bev has got a great big garden
full of vegetables
she picks them and cooks them
and makes us dinner
Come and see what l found
l found a pumpkin
This is a pumpkin
This is a small pumpkin
Then l picked some big pumpkins
The pumkins were very big
And l'm going to put them in this box
And l was going to drop them in it
. . . put them in carefully
Big big pumpkin and
it's a dirty one and
it's a green one and
l'm going to put it right in there
that box there where the m. . .are
Just wipe all the dirt off
Come on lets put it in
They were hard to carry
l put them very carefully
in the pumpkin box
Two of us had to carry the apple box
it was so heavy
It was so heavy cos
it was full of apples
When the boxes were full
we carried everything on to the patio
l sorted everything out
l sorted it all out
Red beans
Green tomatoes
red apples and green apples
green tomatoes and red tomatoes
Green pumpkins
Coriander
Nice thyme
We ate some of the red tomatoes
The tomatoes tasted lovely
l love working in nanny's garden
Bye
Bye bye
Eh - ohhh
One day in Teletubbie Land
Tinky Winky was making Tubby toast
for all the other Teletubbies
Tubby toast Tubby toast
Tubby toast
ho Tubby toast
Tubby toast Toast
Tubby toast Tubby toast
Dipsy hoo-hoo
Tinky Winky
Po
Laa-Laa
Tubby toast Tubby toast
One two three four!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Tinky Winky called Dipsy, Laa-Laa and Po
to tell them their Tubby toast was ready
Tubby toast Tubby toast
Dipsy! Laa-Laa! Po! Tubby toast!
Tubby toast!
Ohhhh
Ohhh Ooo ha-ha
Tubby toast!
Ohhh
Tubby toast
Tubby toast! Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Tubby toast Tubby toast
Dipsy! Laa-Laa! Po! Tubby to - ast!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Dipsy! Laa-Laa! Po!
Tubby toast!
Yeah - h - h!
Eh-oh Dipsy Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Po
Eh-oh Tinky Winky!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast...
Oh
Oh!
Uh-oh-h-h!
Oh Oh
The Tubby toast had gone
Tubby toast - all gone! Uh-ohhh
Tubby toast all gone!
Uh-ohhhh
Where has the Tubby toast gone?
Where Tubby toast gone?
Uh - oh - h - h!
Naughty Noo-Noo
Naughty Noo-Noooo!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Tubby toast!
Yeah! Dipsy toast!
ha-ha! Dipsy toast!
Dipsy toast
Yeah - h - h!
Tinky Winky toast
Po toast! Oo-ray!
hooray! Laa-Laa toast!
hooray!
h'ray!
Tubby toast!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast!
Tubby toast
Ah - h - h! Mmm-ahh!
Tubby toast! Tubby toast
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Ohhhwww No-o-o-o!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Yeah!
No-o-o-o
No-o-o-o!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
By-bye
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
By-bye
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
By-bye
Bye-bye
By - by - y - y!
Bye!
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Tinky Winky
Tinky Winky!
Dipsy
Dipsy!
Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa!
Po
Po!
Teletubbies
Teletubbies!
Say hello!
hello
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Teletubbies
Teletubbies!
Big hug
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Ohhh
Ohh
Shh Shh
Shh
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
hello it's me and my brother
We're making salad
This is my grandma
Time to go shopping now
We're shopping for salad
We're going to buy some tomatoes
Look tomatoes ripe tomatoes
Spring onions
Cucumber
l can see lots of different vegetables
Ask the man how much
here's the money to pay for them
Fifty pence
This is your change
So we have got everything
for our salad haven't we?
We can go home now can't we?
Yes yes
It is time to wash salad now
l am washing the salad in the sink
There's lots of lettuce
and a long cucumber
Lesley likes salad
Do you want some cucumber?
These are lots of cucumbers and
tomatoes
Do you want some salad cream?
Lesley really like salad cream
This is nice
l love tomatoes
Bye bye bye bye
Again again
hello it's me and my brother
We're making salad
This is my grandma
Time to go shopping now
We're shopping for salad
We're going to buy some tomatoes
Look tomatoes ripe tomatoes
Spring onions
Cucumber
l can see lots of different vegetables
Ask the man how much
here's the money to pay for them
Fifty pence
This is your change
So we have got everything
for our salad haven't we?
We can go home now can't we?
Yes yes
It is time to wash salad now
l am washing the salad in the sink
There's lots of lettuce
and a long cucumber
Lesley likes salad
Do you want some cucumber?
These are lots of cucumbers
and tomatoes
Do you want some salad cream?
Lesley really like salad cream
This is nice
l love tomatoes
Bye bye bye bye
Eh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
But then Po fell down from the table
Uh-oh
Uh-oh Po fall down
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
Uh-oh
Uh-oh Po fall down again again
Then all the Teletubbies
fell down from the table
Oh-no
Uh-oh
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
Uh-oh, fall down
Uh-oh fall down
Tubby Custard! Tubby Custard!
Uh-oh
Again again
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh Oh Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo he-he-he Boo he-he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye