Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Uh-oh?
Tubbycustard
Oh! No!
Oh! Oh!
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Oooh, Po
We're going strawberry picking
Come on
We're picking strawberries
You have to look very carefully
to find the strawberries
That's a really, really big strawberry
Strawberries are my favourite
I've got one
Lots and lots and lots
and lots of strawberries
l want to eat one
Who's that?
l want that strawberry.
Guess how many I've got
They're really juicy
Look how many I've got, one, two
There's lots and lots and
lots of strawberries in there
Lots of them I'm sure
Do you want cream
l really love strawberries
Bye
Bye-bye
Owwwww
Again, again, again
We're going strawberry picking
Come on
We're picking strawberries
You have to look very carefully
to find the strawberries
That's a really, really big strawberry
Strawberries are my favourite
I've got one
Lots and lots and lots
and lots of strawberries
l want to eat one
Who's that?
l want that strawberry.
Guess how many I've got
They're really juicy
Look how many I've got, one, two
There's lots and lots and
lots of strawberries in there
Lots of them I'm sure
Do you want cream
l really love strawberries
Bye
Yeah
Yeah!
One day in Teletubby something
appeared from far away
Oh look, look at that
Lovely. Look at that
Uh-oh
Oh, what's that? Oh!
What's that? What's that?
It was a present
Ooooh. It's a present
It's a present. Oh. Oh.
Oh!
It's a present, a present
A present, a present. Oooooh
Oh
l wonder what's inside the present
What's inside the present?
What's inside? What's inside?
It's a present, a present
a present, a present
A present, a present
l wonder who the present is for
Oh! l wonder who the present is for
Maybe the present is for Tinky Winky
Maybe the present is for Dipsy
Oh!
Or maybe the present is for Po.
Oh
Maybe the present is for Po
Or maybe the present is for Laa-Laa
Oh yes
Maybe the present is for Laa-Laa
Quick have a look at the label
Oh
Quick. have a look at the label
Quick. Quick
Oh Dipsy
The present is for Dipsy
hey, the present is for Dipsy
The present is for Dipsy. Dipsy!
Dipsy
Oh Laa-Laa
Yes
It's a present
Pardon?
It's a present for Dipsy
ls it for Dipsy?
Oh. What's that?
It's a present
It's for Dipsy
Oh!
Dipsy. Dipsy
Oh
Dipsy look
Oh!
This is for Dipsy
It's a Dipsy present
Oh a Dipsy present
Yes. What's inside the present?
Oh Dipsy. Oh. Dipsy! Dipsy!
here you are
Laa-Laa opens the present, yes
Oh
A present. It's a present
A present. A present
Oh
Look
Oh!
What's that?
A lovely decoration for Dipsy's hat
Oh, it's a lovely decoration
for Dipsy's hat
hat, hat, hat
Doesn't it look lovely
Uh-oh
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo, he-he-he. Boo he-he
Boo boo boo. Boo, boo
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh
Uh-oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
hello, hello, hello, hello
hello, my name is Will
This is my sister Leah
We're picking oranges
There's my grandpa
Oh, good one
Grandpa, you want to pick some?
OK, put one in Leah's bucket
Will's getting some real good oranges
This one
Ok, yes
One, two
Yes, good one
Three. One, two, three
Ok Leah
You want Grandpa to help you
Ok I'll lift you up and
we'll get higher on the tree OK
They are higher
Yes, we may have to get a ladder later
¡ºhank you Leah. That's a good job, that's a good job
Oh, this is a nice orange Leah
look at that one
The bucket's full
come on, come on
Come on Leah
We can peel this orange
Yes
l peel the skin
Do you want Grandpa
to help you with this one?
Look at the peelings come off
Ok Will, stick your thumb in there
Break it in half
There you go
Do you want a bite Leah?
ls that juicy? Yes
Put your thumb in there
and break that one off
There's loads of juice
There you go
We like oranges!
Bye
Good bye
Again, again
hello, hello, hello, hello
hello, my name is Will
This is my sister Leah
We're picking oranges
There's my grandpa
Oh, good one
Grandpa, you want to pick some?
OK, put one in Leah's bucket
Will's getting some real good oranges
This one
Ok, yes
One, two
Yes, good one
Three. One, two, three
Ok Leah
You want Grandpa to help you
Ok I'll lift you up and
we'll get higher on the tree OK
They are higher
Yes, we may have to get a ladder later
¡ºhank you Leah. That's a good job, that's a good job
Oh, this is a nice orange Leah
look at that one
The bucket's full
come on, come on
Come on Leah
We can peel this orange
Yes
l peel the skin
Do you want Grandpa
to help you with this one?
Look at the peelings come off
Ok Will, stick your thumb in there
Break it in half
There you go
Do you want a bite Leah?
ls that juicy? Yes
Put your thumb in there
and break that one off
There's loads of juice
There you go
We like oranges!
Bye
Good bye
Eh-oh
One day in Teletubbyland
Tinky Winky and Po
were eating Tubby Toast
Tubby Toast
Eh-oh
Eh-oh Laa-Laa
Eh-oh Tinky Winky, Eh-oh Po
Laa-Laa came to play
with her ball indoors
Laa-Laa ball indoors
Ohh
Laa-Laa ball
Ohhh
Uh-oh!
Look!
Laa-Laa's ball was stuck
Laa-Laa's ball is stuck
Laa-Laa ball stuck, oh dear
Laa-Laa asked Tinky Winky
if he could reach her ball
Oh
Tinky Winky
Yes
Tinky Winky Laa-Laa ball
Tinky Winky couldn't reach the ball
Tinky Winky can't reach
Tinky Winky not reach, uh-oh
Ohhh
Po thought she could reach the ball
Po reach ball
Ohh
Po reaches Laa-Laa's ball
but Laa-Laa's ball was still stuck
Still stuck
Uh-oh
And then the Noo-noo tidies up
Noo-noo tidy up
Ohh
Uh-oh!
Noo-noo
hooray
Laa-Laa's ball
Laa-Laa ball
Clever Noo-noo
Laa-Laa loves her ball
Laa-Laa ball
And Teletubbies love
the Noo-noo very much
Love Noo-noo, big hug
Big hug Noo-noo
Big hug
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
Boo, he-he-he
Boo he-he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye