Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Two.
Three.
Four.
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies.
Uh-oh.
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Wooaa!
Weeee!
Yeahh, weeee!
Eh oh.
Weeee!
Uh oh.
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Ohhh, Tinky Winky!
We're going on a train
This is my mummy
Good morning, can l help you
Please can l have three tickets
to Glasgow central
That'll be ?3.80 please
Four, five
Thank you.
Thank you, enjoy your train ride, bye
Thank you bye
Bye
Look at this, look Amy
here comes our train
The train is coming
Oh, yeah
Train is coming
train is coming
The train is moving
Tickets, please
have you got your tickets please
Thank you
he put holes in our tickets
Thank you.
Thank you
Nana, look over there
you can see the shops
. . . .cars.
l see
Big one.
Tall flats
A tall one
We're in a tunnel
We're going under a tunnel
There's some nice white houses up here
Yes
. . .do you like them
Yeah
We're going over a bridge. . . .
l like going over bridges
Look at the railway lines
. . . .a bridge
We're . . . .
We're going over another bridge
We're going to see . . .
The train is going down
some more and some more
The train is docking
We're here
Bye, bye train
Bye
Eh oh.
Ohh! Again again again
Again again again
Ssh, ssh, ssh, ssh!
We're going on a train
This is my mummy
Good morning, can l help you
Please can l have three tickets
to Glasgow central
That'll be ?3.80 please
Four, five
Thank you.
Thank you, enjoy your train ride, bye
Thank you bye
Bye
Look at this, look Amy
here comes our train
The train is coming
Oh, yeah
Train is coming
train is coming
The train is moving
Tickets, please
have you got your tickets please
Thank you
he put holes in our tickets
Thank you.
Thank you
Nana, look over there
you can see the shops
. . . .cars.
l see
Big one.
Tall flats
A tall one
We're in a tunnel
We're going under a tunnel
There's some nice white houses up here
Yes
. . .do you like them
Yeah
We're going over a bridge. . . .
l like going over bridges
Look at the railway lines
. . . .a bridge
We're . . . .
We're going over another bridge
We're going to see . . .
The train is going down
some more and some more
The train is docking
We're here
Bye, bye train
Bye
Eh oh.
One day in Teletubby land
Po was happily riding
her scooter all over the hills
Over the hills
When a big squeak came.
Ohh!
Oh, eh oh. Eh oh.
Po.
Eh oh Tinky Winky.
Eh oh Po.
Big hug.
Eh oh.
Oh, Po, Po, Po.
Eh oh Dipsy.
Eh oh Po. Po.
Big hug.
Eh oh.
Ooh what's that?
Po
Eh oh Laa-Laa.
Eh oh Po.
Ahh, big hug
Po was feeling very very very happy
Very very very happy.
"ook. Ahh!
Ahh, ahh, ahh! !
Oh, what's that?
Po noticed that her scooter had gone
Oh! Uh oh!
Oh no, "cooter gone.
Po, Po.
Oh, where Po?
Po.
Where Po?
Oh, oh!
Po's scooter came back.
"cooter. Aah!
And the big squeak went away.
Ohh!
Teletubbies love each other very much.
Big hug.
Aah!
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Time for Tubby bye-bye.
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One.
Two
Three
Four
Four.
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubbycustard
Tubbycustard, Tubbycustard
Be careful Po
you are spilling your Tubbycustard
Ohhhhhh
Oh dear
Tubbycustard, Tubbycustard
Be careful Laa-Laa
don't tread in the Tubbycustard
Tubbycustard! Tubbycustard
Tubbycustard, Tubbycustard
Be careful Dipsy
don't tread in the Tubbycustard
Uh-oh, be careful Dipsy
Tubbycustard, Tubbycustard
Be careful Tinky Winky
don't tread in the Tubbycustard
Tinky Winky slipped
in the Tubbycustard
Oh dear
Tinky Winky slipped in the Tubbycustard
Eh-oh!
Uh-oh
Tubbycustard,
Tubbycustard
Eh-oh! Noo-Noo
Thank you Noo-noo
Tinky Winky
Tubbycustard
Oh no
Tinky Winky hasn't got
any Tubbycustard left
No Tubbycustard left
Ahhhhhh
here are Tinky Winky
Ahh Dipsy
Thank you Dipsy
Tubbycustard, Tubbycustard
Owwwwww
hello, hello.
Come and see us skate
lce skating.
My name is Natalie. l love skating
My name is Fluella
My name is Shauna
l just started to skate
Sometimes l fall over
but it doesn't hurt
I'm skating with Shauna
Shauna skates very carefully
l like skating backwards with Shauna
l like skating with Laura.
l like skating holding hands
Ring a ring a roses
Pocket full of posies
Atishoo, atishoo
We all fall down.
My name is Franki
Watch me skating
My name is Vivian
My name is Amy
l like dancing on the ice
I'm . . . .dance with Amy
I'm the fastest skater
l like skating really fast
Bye, bye
Again, again
hello, hello.
Come and see us skate
lce skating.
My name is Natalie. l love skating
My name is Fluella
My name is Shauna
l just started to skate
Sometimes l fall over
but it doesn't hurt
I'm skating with Shauna
Shauna skates very carefully
l like skating backwards with Shauna
l like skating with Laura.
l like skating holding hands
Ring a ring a roses
Pocket full of posies
Atishoo, atishoo
We all fall down.
My name is Franki
Watch me skating
My name is Vivian
My name is Amy
l like dancing on the ice
I'm . . . .dance with Amy
I'm the fastest skater
l like skating really fast
Bye, bye
Eh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland
Po and Tinky Winky
decided to hold hands
Po
Tinky Winky
holding hands
hold hands
Eh-oh!
So Dipsy and Laa-Laa
decided to hold hands too
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
hold hands
And Dipsy decided to
hold hands with Po
Po
Dipsy
Tinky Winky decided to
hold hands with Laa-Laa
Laa-Laa
Tinky Winky
Then all the Teletubbies
were holding hands
Teletubbies holding hands
Yeeee
Uh-oh
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo! (Laughs)
Boo, he-he-he. Boo he-he-he.
No
No.
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye.
Bye-bye