Over the hills and far away,
Teletubbies come to play.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies.
Uh-oh.
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Uh-oh!
Eh-oh!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy.
Laa-Laa.
Po.
Oooh, Dipsy.
hello
hello, my name is Jenny
come and meet my mummy
My mummy's a doctor
If you're poorly she makes you better
Are you coming with me
Not yet
why don't you come and sit down
while l just finish what l'm doing
Mummys a doctor.
When you're not feeling very wel
l first of all you go and see my mummy
My mummy's very special
she can make people feel better
My mummy uses this torch
to look in your ears and mouth.
Do you want me to check for you
Yes
Shall we, let's have a look
tilt your head like this
l'll shine this torch in your ear
and look to see
if it's red cost sometimes
if ears are poorly they go very red
and then we can give people
some medicine to make them better
That one's fine though
When children come and
they're poorly do you know
what else we have to look at
Well we have to look at their throat
to see if they've got a poorly throat
Shall l show you what l do
Can you turn round and look at me
And you say Ahhh.
Ahhh.
And you tilt your head up.
And l can see right down
and you say ahh
Ahh.
That's a good girl
oh, that looks very healthy
And the other thing that
we do is we get them
to blow into this special machine
l can do that
Do you
Yeh.
Right so what you need to do
is you need to go big blow
Good right up there
have another go.
That means that
your lungs are very healthy
Your chest is very healthy
you can blow all the way up there
That's very good
l know mummy
give me a tum tum check
OK, let's go and check your tummy
That always makes me giggle.
Shall l listen to your chest first
Listen to you breathing
Yes
That's it
Now have a listen with this
Big breath in now
Nice and slowly
And again, again.
And again.
My mummy does a tum tum check
she listens to noises
with a stethoscope
She can listen to
noises in your tummy
OK. Shall we do your tummy
What can we feel here
can't feel any breakfast
can't feel your lunch
You've got a very little
tummy haven't you
And it tickles me
l think you're missing your
lacking your tea
l think you need your tea
Feels fine otherwise
shall we take you home for tea now
Yes
Come on then let's get you down
l love my mummy
l love to seem my mummy
when she's a doctor
Bye
Bye-bye.
Owwwww.
hello
hello, my name is Jenny
come and meet my mummy
My mummy's a doctor
If you're poorly she makes you better
Are you coming with me
Not yet
why don't you come and sit down
while l just finish what l'm doing
Mummys a doctor.
When you're not feeling very wel
l first of all you go and see my mummy
My mummy's very special
she can make people feel better
My mummy uses this torch
to look in your ears and mouth.
Do you want me to check for you
Yes
Shall we, let's have a look
tilt your head like this
l'll shine this torch in your ear
and look to see
if it's red cost sometimes
if ears are poorly they go very red
and then we can give people
some medicine to make them better
That one's fine though
When children come and
they're poorly do you know
what else we have to look at
Well we have to look at their throat
to see if they've got a poorly throat
Shall l show you what l do
Can you turn round and look at me
And you say Ahhh.
Ahhh.
And you tilt your head up.
And l can see right down
and you say ahh
Ahh.
That's a good girl
oh, that looks very healthy
And the other thing that
we do is we get them
to blow into this special machine
l can do that
Do you
Yeh.
Right so what you need to do
is you need to go big blow
Good right up there
have another go.
That means that
your lungs are very healthy
Your chest is very healthy
you can blow all the way up there
That's very good
l know mummy
give me a tum tum check
OK, let's go and check your tummy
That always makes me giggle.
Shall l listen to your chest first
Listen to you breathing
Yes
That's it
Now have a listen with this
Big breath in now
Nice and slowly
And again, again.
And again.
My mummy does a tum tum check
she listens to noises
with a stethoscope
She can listen to
noises in your tummy
OK. Shall we do your tummy
What can we feel here
can't feel any breakfast
can't feel your lunch
You've got a very little
tummy haven't you
And it tickles me
l think you're missing your
lacking your tea
l think you need your tea
Feels fine otherwise
shall we take you home for tea now
Yes
Come on then let's get you down
l love my mummy
l love to seem my mummy
when she's a doctor
Bye
One day in Teletubbyland
it was time for Tubby custard.
hello.
Tubby custard. Tubby custard.
Po was feeling very hungry.
Very hungry.
Tubby custard. Tubby custard.
Po likes Tubby custard very much.
Oh Tubby custard.
Tubby custard. Ah.
Po went to get some more.
Po likes Tubby custard.
Again, again, again, again.
Again, again, again.
Tubby custard.
Ah! Tubby custard.
Po likes Tubby custard
very, very much.
Po likes Tubby custard.
Again, again.
Po went to get some more.
Tubby custard. Tubby custard.
Po likes Tubby custard
very, very, very much.
Po likes Tubby custard.
Again, again.
Tubby custard. Tubby custard.
Tubby custard.
Tubby custard. Tubby custard. Oh!
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh dear.
Oh dear Po.
Tubby custard tummy. Sometimes
if the Teletubbies eat too much
Tubby custard and they
eat their Tubby custard too fast
they get Tubby custard tummy.
Oh Tubby custard tummy
Oh dear.
hello. hello Po
hello Laa-Laa
Oh. Oh dear
Oh dear. Oh
Oh dear Tubby custard tummy
Oh. Oh dear Tubby custard tummy
Oh
Oh Po
here you are Po
Oh dear. Oh dear. Oh dear Po
Tubby custard tummy
Tubby custard tummy.
Oh dear. Oh dear. Oh dear
Oh! Oh! All gone
Tubby custard tummy
All gone
Yes
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po.
Boo!
Boo, he-he-he. Boo he-he
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa.
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh-oh!
Uh-oh!
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa.
Po
Oh oh look oh
Oooh Dipsy yeah
hello, hello, hello
My name is Olivia
and when l'm grown up
l want to be a vet
which is an animal doctor
come and see.
hello, Olivia
what can l do for you today
l want to see Michelle
Michelle. You want to see Michelle
Would you like to take a seat
and l'll tell her you're here
hello Michelle
l've got Olivia to see you
OK Olivia
would you like to
bring Thumper through
OK. Can you manage.
Oh, yes
Come on then
have you been in this room before
Do you still want to be a vet Olivia
Oh, yes
Do you want to help me do that.
Yes. lt's Thumper isn't it
Take his food out
you coming out Thumper
They don't like coming out too much
because the're a bit
worried about coming out
OK. how can l help you
today with Thumper
have a look at his teeth
has he been eating his food OK
Yes but l just want to see
if his teeth are too long
OK, well l'll have
a look at his teeth
ls he a friendly rabbit
Oh, yes
Stop being such a naughty boy Thumper
Right now you're going to
have to hold onto him
so we can do tha
hold tight now.
and l'll manage to
open his mouth l think
You know you would have
to do this if youwere a vet
Oh, yes
These teeth are nice
and they're not too long
Can you see them.
Yes you can come
and have a look and see his teeth
They're not too long are they
No, they're not too long
Anything else you want me to look at
Are his claws too long.
OK, we'll have a look and see
We'll have a look at your claws
No they're not too bad today
but we could clip the ends off
..won't l.
OK. Oh, he's being
a good boy now isn't he
This doesn't hurt
Does it hurt you
when you cut your nails
No.
Ah, so it doesn't hurt him
But he doesn't know that at first.
OK, well we'll put him back
in the box now
Come on Thumper.
l haven't got a favourite
on l like them all
That's like me
l like them all as well
OK Thumper do you
want to get in the back
We'll shut that door
so he doesn't come out
Right, will l help you out with him
l'll take him out for you. OK
Bye.
Bye-bye
Owwwwwwwwww
Again, again, again
Yeah
hello, hello, hello
My name is Olivia
and when l'm grown up
l want to be a vet
which is an animal doctor
come and see.
hello, Olivia
what can l do for you today
l want to see Michelle
Michelle. You want to see Michelle
Would you like to take a seat
and l'll tell her you're here
hello Michelle
l've got Olivia to see you
OK Olivia
would you like to
bring Thumper through
OK. Can you manage.
Oh, yes
Come on then
have you been in this room before
Do you still want to be a vet Olivia
Oh, yes
Do you want to help me do that.
Yes. lt's Thumper isn't it
Take his food out
you coming out Thumper
They don't like coming out too much
because the're a bit
worried about coming out
OK. how can l help you
today with Thumper
have a look at his teeth
has he been eating his food OK
Yes but l just want to see
if his teeth are too long
OK, well l'll have
a look at his teeth
ls he a friendly rabbit
Oh, yes
Stop being such a naughty boy Thumper
Right now you're going to
have to hold onto him
so we can do tha
hold tight now.
and l'll manage to
open his mouth l think
You know you would have
to do this if youwere a vet
Oh, yes
These teeth are nice
and they're not too long
Can you see them.
Yes you can come
and have a look and see his teeth
They're not too long are they
No, they're not too long
Anything else you want me to look at
Are his claws too long.
OK, we'll have a look and see
We'll have a look at your claws
No they're not too bad today
but we could clip the ends off
..won't l.
OK. Oh, he's being
a good boy now isn't he
This doesn't hurt
Does it hurt you
when you cut your nails
No.
Ah, so it doesn't hurt him
But he doesn't know that at first.
OK, well we'll put him back
in the box now
Come on Thumper.
l haven't got a favourite
on l like them all
That's like me
l like them all as well
OK Thumper do you
want to get in the back
We'll shut that door
so he doesn't come out
Right, will l help you out with him
l'll take him out for you. OK
Bye.
Eh-oh!
One day in Teletubbyland Po
heard Laa-Laa coming
Oh
Laa-Laa coming
And do you know what Po decided
to play a hiding game
Ssssssssh
Sssssssssh
Eh-oh!
Laa-Laa wondered where Po was
Where's Po? Where's Po?
Laa-Laa could see Po's scooter
Look
But where was Po?
Where's the Po?
Sssssssssh.
Where's Po?
""Boo,'' said Po
Boo
What a surprise!
What a surprise
Po was hiding
Po and Laa-Laa heard Dipsy coming
Uh-oh!
So Po and Laa-Laa decided to
play a hiding game
Ssssssh
Sssssh
Uh-oh!
Psssst. Psst
Oh. Sssssssssh
Ssssssssssssh.
Eh-oh!
Dipsy wondered
where Po and Laa-Laa were
Dipsy could see Po's scooter
and Laa-Laa's ball
but where were Po and Laa-Laa
Oh Laa-Laa's ball
Po's scooter
Where's Po and Laa-Laa
Sssssssssh
Where's Po and Laa-Laa?
""Boo,'' said Po
""Boo,'' said Laa-Laa
Boo!
What a surprise!
Po and Laa-Laa were hiding
hiding, hiding, hiding
Dipsy, Laa-Laa and Po heard
Tinky Winky coming
Oh
Uh-oh!
So they decided to
play a hiding game
Ssssssh
Sssssssh
Eh-oh!
Tinky Winky wondered where Po
and Laa-Laa and Dipsy where
Where Po, Laa-Laa and Dipsy?
Tinky Winky could see the scooter
the ball and the hat
Scooter, ball, hat
But where were Po
Laa-Laa and Dipsy?
Where Po, Laa-Laa and Dipsy?
""Boo,'' said Po
""Boo,'' said Laa-Laa
""Boo,'' said Dipsy
Boo!
What a surprise!
Surprise!
Po, Laa-Laa and Dipsy were hiding
hiding, hiding, hiding
Tinky Winky, Dipsy, Laa-Laa
and Po heard the Noo Noo coming
Noo Noo
Uh-oh!
So they decided to
play a hiding game
Sssssssh
Uh-oh!
Psssst
The Noo Noo wondered
where the Teletubbies were
The Noo Noo could see the scooter
the ball, the hat and the bag
But the Teletubbies had gone
Laa-Laa's ball
Oh no!
Oh!
Dipsy's hat
Tinky Winky's bag
Uh-oh!
Naughty Noo Noo
Time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo!
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Bye-bye.
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye