Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh.
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
Eh oh
One day in Teletubby land
it was time for Tubby custard
Oh, Tubby custard
Tubby custard
Oooh!
Custard, aah!
Custard, custard, custard
Oooh!
Yay. Yay
Tubby custard, yay
l like Tubby custard
Oh
Yay, Tubby custard
Tubby custard
Oooh!
Yay, Tubby custard.
Tubby custard
Tubby custard, get this out!
Ooh, Tubby custard.
Oooh!
Tubby custard.
Tubby custard
Uh oh
Oooh!
The Teletubbies decided to
bounce like the ball
Ooh, bounce like a ball
Teletubbies, be careful with
your Tubby custard
Boing, boing, boing, boing
Tubby custard, tubby custard, ugh!
Oh no
Uh oh
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa-Laa
Po
Oh Tinky Winky
hello, hello, hello
hello
Would you like to help
One day Ned helped
granny lift potatoes
Colander
You're going to carry the colander
and I'll carry the fork or will you
You help me to carry the fork
l can do it
l'm having it on my own
l can
Oh, you are such a help
Flowers today
Where shall we start
shall we start here
Push this down, push it down
Push it down, push it right down
That's right. That's good
Now where are the potatoes
Even.
ln colander
Tato
You going to help me push in again
stopping
Yes
We dig it
Digging tatos
l wonder whether there
will be any underneat
Are there any
Yeh
There's the tatos
Two here grandma
One, two, three
Are there any more
are there any more
Yes
That's the biggest
Love it
That's a tiny, tiny one
Tiny, that's a tiny one
Can you carry the colander
Very heavy
It is very heavy are you all right
with it or shall l help you
I'll help you
Lots of it's heavy
Now we can get the water shall we
l'm washing the tatoes
They're still dirty
have a look
l'm washing my hands
Yes
We're going to take the tatoes inside
Bye. Goodbye
Goodbye, goodbye
Goodbye
Bye
Eh oh
Bye-bye
Owwwww.
Again, again, again.
hello
Eh oh
hello, hello, hello
hello
Would you like to help
One day Ned helped
granny lift potatoes
Colander
You're going to carry the colander
and I'll carry the fork or will you
You help me to carry the fork
l can do it
l'm having it on my own
l can
Oh, you are such a help
Flowers today
Where shall we start
shall we start here
Push this down, push it down
Push it down, push it right down
That's right. That's good
Now where are the potatoes
Even.
ln colander
Tato
You going to help me push in again
stopping
Yes
We dig it
Digging tatos
l wonder whether there
will be any underneat
Are there any
Yeh
There's the tatos
Two here grandma
One, two, three
Are there any more
are there any more
Yes
That's the biggest
Love it
That's a tiny, tiny one
Tiny, that's a tiny one
Can you carry the colander
Very heavy
It is very heavy are you all right
with it or shall l help you
I'll help you
Lots of it's heavy
Now we can get the water shall we
l'm washing the tatoes
They're still dirty
have a look
l'm washing my hands
Yes
We're going to take the tatoes inside
Bye. Goodbye
Goodbye, goodbye
Goodbye
Bye
Wooh, Tinka Winka. . . ..
Weeee!
Whay!
Ohh!
Uh oh, oh dear
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Uh oh
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Time for Tubby bye-bye.
Oh. Oh. Oh no
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo! (laughs)
Boo!
Boo, he-he-he
Boo he-he
Boo boo boo
Boo, boo
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye
Over the hills and far away
Teletubbies come to play
One
Two
Three
Four
Four.
Teletubbies!
Time for Teletubbies
Uh-oh!
Where have the Teletubbies gone?
E-oh!
One, two, three
Tinky Winky
Dipsy
Laa Laa
Po
hello, hello, hello,hello,hello
Owwwwwww
Come on
l'm making hot chocolate
This is the caf¨¦
There are other customers
and they get their food
and drinks from there
She makes all of them a drink
Sandy, can you get me a jug down
l'm making hot chocolate now
Yeh
It's quite heavy
l get it off
l get some chocolate
Spooning the chocolate
lnto the jug.
The milk. Now l stir it
Sandy
Nice big bubble
l think that's nice
the customers and me drink it
l'm going to see if it's all right
It's not quite
Got a few more lumps
One more spoonful
There's a mountain on top
You can do it up and down or round
It's ready
We need some hot milk
Nice
Goodbye
Again
Come on
l'm making hot chocolate
This is the caf¨¦
There are other customers
and they get their food
and drinks from there
She makes all of them a drink
Sandy, can you get me a jug down
l'm making hot chocolate now
Yeh
It's quite heavy
l get it off
l get some chocolate
Spooning the chocolate
lnto the jug.
The milk. Now l stir it
Sandy
Nice big bubble
l think that's nice
the customers and me drink it
l'm going to see if it's all right
It's not quite
Got a few more lumps
One more spoonful
There's a mountain on top
You can do it up and down or round
It's ready
We need some hot milk
Nice
Goodbye
Weeeeeeee!
Weeeeeeeee!
One day in Teletubby land
it was time for Tubby Custard
Tubby Custard!
Laa Laa
Oh no
Again, again
Yeah!
Tubby Custard!
Nice!
And do you know
after all that custard
the Teletubbies
were very full up
Full up
Uh-oh!
Time for Tubby Bye-bye
time for Tubby bye-bye
Oh. Oh. Oh no!
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
Boo! (Laughs)
Boo, he-he-he. Boo he-he-he.
No
Bye-bye Tinky Winky
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Dipsy
Bye-bye Laa-Laa
Bye-bye
Bye-bye Po
The sun is setting in the sky
Teletubbies say goodbye
Bye-bye